皓瀚霏凡 作品
-=圣城家园 CnSCG 荣誉出品=-
http://hd.cnscg.com
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
校对:月光取暖 心仪Sally   协调:心仪Sally
翻译:景鲤 RK翔 hangubing 小粥粥 小FA 八月的冬天 心仪Sally
香       港
- All eyes are up.  - Sat cams are good.
- 一切就绪  - 摄像头就位
Target is inbound.
目标已入境
ETA five minutes.
预订到达时间为五分钟
Mission is a go. Repeat, you are green to go.
任务开始 重复一下 你们可以开始行动了
Intercept and apprehend the Heinrich brothers.
拦截然后逮捕海因里希兄弟俩
Secure the device. And remember, this mission is covert.
保护好装备 记住 这是次秘密任务
I've got some action.
我要开始行动了
- Hi, my name is Xenia.  - Pleased to meet you. I'm Tuck.
- 嗨 我是齐妮亚  - 很高兴认识你 我是塔克
FDR.
我是富兰克林
So, what brings you to Hong Kong?
你为什么来香港啊?
- Business or pleasure?  - Pleasure.
- 公事还是私事?  - 私事
- Business.  - A little of both.
- 公事  - 算是公私兼顾
What kind of business?
什么样的公事?
I am a cruise ship captain of a very large vessel.
我是一只大型船舰的游艇船长
My small friend here is a kick-ass travel agent.
我的这位朋友是个厉害的旅行社代理人
Permission to come aboard, captain?
允许我们登船吗 船长?
On that note, will you excuse us, ladies, because we do have work to do.
关于这一点 请允许我们失陪一下 女士们 我们要办正事了
- No, we don't.  - Yes, we do.
- 不 不用吧  - 我们确实要办正事了
Yes, we do.
哦 是的
That's a lovely suit.
这套西装真不错
Well, it is Savile Row's finest.
当然了 这是萨维尔街的上等货
I see you brought your baby brother to protect you.
我看你把你亲爱的兄弟带来保护你
What did you say?
你说什么?
Let's go, Jonas.
我们走吧 乔纳斯
Shots fired. Men down.
有人开枪了 那些人倒了
All right. Here we go.
好了 我们开始了
Mag. I need a mag.
弹夹 我需要子弹
Shoot him.
开枪啊
Tuck!
塔克!
Jonas!
乔纳斯!
- Heinrich is not gonna be happy.  - I'm more concerned about the boss.
- 海因里希不会高兴的  - 我更关心老板的看法
Definitely. Hey, you think those girls are still here?
当然了 嘿 你觉得那些姑娘还在那里吗?
情敌大战
# I need good love #
我想要好好爱一场
# In my head #
在我的脑海里
# Before you came along #
在你出现之前
# I felt like I was dead #
我如同行尸走肉
# I got good love #
我们找到了真爱
# Rock 'n' roll #
一起摇滚吧
# Well, I met a sweet girl #
我邂逅了位美丽的女孩
# She blew my mind #
她让我无法自拔
# And we've been hangin' out #
我们也一直在约会
# Ever since that time #
从那次之后
# We got good love #
我们找到了真爱
# Rock 'n' roll #
一起摇滚吧
# Oh, yeah #
哦 就这样
# Sweet, sweet love #
甜蜜蜜的爱
明智消费公司
Here we go. So the Coretex has minimal damage.
开始了 那么这个"硬壳"损坏最小
洛杉矶・加州
There's some calcining around the edges.
边缘处有些烧伤
However, the Tempolite has damage and there's rusting around 300 degrees.
但是 "样板"大约有300度的锈蚀损伤
So that means the Coretex gets the recommend.
那也就是说推荐"硬壳"了
See, Em? The best product always wins.
看见了吧? 最好的产品总是赢家
- Oh, Lauren.  - Yes.
- 喔 劳拉  - 嗯
I was just wondering if I might skip out a little bit early for the holiday weekend.
我在想我能不能早点下班去过这个周末的假期呢
Jerry's taking me to an alpaca farm.
杰瑞要带我去羊驼农场
Oh, yeah, of course. It's a holiday. And a weekend.
哦 好吧 当然了 放假嘛 又是周末
Yeah, so you should do that.
那么 你可以早点走
- Okay.  - Have fun.
- 好的  - 玩得开心点
- You have fun too.  - I will.
- 你也玩得开心  - 会的
中央情报局外勤办公室
Tuck. FDR.
塔克 富兰克林
Six men in the morgue.
停尸间里有六具尸体
A body in the middle of the street.
路中间还有一个
Yes, but to be fair, we did manage to...
是的 但说句实在话 我们确实成功地...
- Shut up.  - To... That's me shutting up, right now.
- 闭嘴  - 成功地... 我这就闭嘴了
The mission parameters of the Heinrich case...
这次有关海因里希的案子
...were clearly indicated to be covert.
很清楚地表明了是秘密任务
Thanks to you two geniuses...
真是多谢你们这两个天才
...Heinrich will be seeking revenge for his brother's death.
海因里希会为他兄弟的死报仇的
You guys are grounded.
你们被禁足了
- What?  - Grounded?
- 什么?  - 禁足?
And just maybe.
可能吧
I'm gonna make it.
我还是会成功的
I'm gonna shake it.
我要摇摆
- Hey, Lauren. Lauren. Hey, hey.  - Oh, oh!
- 嘿 劳拉 劳拉 嘿 喂  - 噢!
Hi, Steve, hey.
嘿 史蒂夫 你好
Hey. It's Steve.
- 嘿  - 是史蒂夫呀
Yeah. Oh, my... I'm so sorry. Uh, Lauren, this is Kelly.
是的 噢 我的... 真抱歉 额 劳伦 这是凯利
- Hi.  - Hi.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- It's very nice to meet you.  - Nice to meet you too, yeah.
- 很高兴认识你  - 我也是
- Wow, ha, ha, what a big rock.  - Yeah.
- 哇 哈哈 钻戒真大啊  - 是啊
My fiance, yes. Yeah.
恩 这是我的未婚妻
- You are engaged.  - Yeah.
- 你订婚了呀  - 是呀
To be married.
就要结婚了
Things just worked out exactly how they're supposed to, didn't they?
事情正如我们预料地那样发展着 不是吗?
Yeah. Yeah.
是呀 是呀
Yes.
嗯
Looks cool.
看上去不错
Okay, well, you know what?
好了 知道不
I'm gonna go because I'm gonna go meet my guy, Ken.
我要走了 因为我要去见我的真命天子肯恩了
- Huh.  - Uh, he's a surgeon.
- 哈  - 额 他是个外科医生
- Wow.  - So, great, well...
- 哇哦  - 那么 好吧...
um, congratulations on your ring and...
额 恭喜你的婚事顺利...
- Oh, thanks.  - and your life...
- 噢 多谢了  - 生活愉快...
- and your bikes and everything.  - Yeah.
- 还有你的自行车和你的一切  - 好的
Okay. Well, peace.
那好了 走吧
- See you.  - Okay. Bye.
- 拜拜  - 好的 拜拜
I just said "peace." I want to die right now.
我刚刚说了"走呗" 我现在真想去死
Sushi for one.
来一份寿司
Hey, Ken.
嘿 肯恩
- The usual?  - Yeah.
- 老样子?  - 是的
- Long day, huh?  - You don't know the half of it.
- 漫长的一天吧?  - 你不会了解的
This is too funny.
真有趣
Hysterical.
真是异常惊喜啊
I'm sorry. This must be your boyfriend's seat. Uh, Ken, right?
很抱歉 这肯定是你男朋友的位子吧 额 叫肯恩 对吧?
- Oh, yeah.  - No.
- 哦 是的  - 不是呀
Sushi for one. Yeah. Always for one.
一人份的寿司 她总是一个人来
Ugh! It was the most humiliating moment ever.
呸 那真是有史以来最丢脸的瞬间
Well, because you have to come up with, like, better excuses.
好吧 因为你得想一些更好的借口
You should've been, "I have a fiance too. But he's getting a penile reduction...
你应该这么说"我也有未婚夫了 不巧他做缩阳手术去啦...
because his penis is so big every time it lands like a poltergeist."
因为他那玩意儿实在太巨大了 大得调皮啊"
Can't think of anything when I see him.
我一看到他就压根不能思考
I just can't believe I gave up everything for him.
真不敢相信我为他放弃了一切
It's just, I felt so stupid. I left my friends, my family...
我只是觉得太笨了 我离开了我的朋友 我的家人...
Don't say that, I'm happy you moved here. We have a happy life together.
别这么说 我很高兴你搬到这来了 我们一起生活得很开心
He was my person.
他曾是我的另一半
He was your person. You know what kind of person he ended up?
我过去也觉得他是你的另一半 你知道他最后会跟什么样的人在一起吗?
The person that ends up with a girl that makes out after she eats yellowtail.
会和那种吃了鲱鱼之后亲热的姑娘在一起
I like sushi. She seemed really nice. She was really pretty.
我喜欢寿司 她看上去很友善 也很漂亮
Well, I don't give a shit about her. I give a shit about you and your love life.
好了 我可不在乎她 我在乎的是你和你的生活
I'm going out, dating, meeting guys.
我一直都在社交 约会 见男孩子啊
Oh, please, you're not... You date, but you're not taking it seriously.
噢 拜托了 你不是... 你是有约会 但是你并没有认真对待
Don't use that brand, it leaves a film. That one's much more effective.
不要用那个牌子 那个洗不干净 那个牌子的要更有效一点
I wish you would act like that with men.
我希望你跟男人在一起的时候也能那样表现
You can choose a laundry detergent, but you can't choose a guy you want...
你可以挑选出洗衣液 却选不出你想要的男人...
That's my job. It's easier. There's charts, there's numbers.
那是我的工作 更容易点 有图表也有数字来对比
That's why you start online dating. They have lots of charts.
这就是你开始网上约会原因 他们都有很多绘制的图表
- Not that again.  - What is your problem with online dating?
- 别再提那个了  - 你在网上约会有什么问题呀?
What's my problem? Do you watch Dateline?
我有什么问题? 你看"约会时间"吗?
How many creeps are out there?
那里有多少变态的家伙?
I could end up a skin suit or in somebody's trunk.
我可能会在某个人的后备箱里穿着皮西装醒来
Uh, that's a little dramatic, okay? That happens to, like, one in 20 girls.
额 那可真是戏剧化了 好吗? 20个姑娘里差不多只有1个会碰到这种情况吧
You're not gonna end up in a trunk. If you're lucky...
你不会死在后备箱里的 如果你走运的话...
somebody will end up in your trunk. That's your trunk.
有人会死在你的后备箱了 那就是你的箱子了
Ha, ha. Stop.
哈哈 够了
You need to get back out there, okay?
你得从那里回来 行不?
because, yeah, sure, you might make a mistake and end up with the wrong guy...
因为 当然了 你也可能会犯错 碰上不合适的人...
but you might end up meeting the right guy. So isn't that worth it?
但是你也可能最后遇上真命天子 难道不值得吗?
What is the worst thing that could happen?
最糟糕的情况会是什么?
Skin suit. Skin suit's pretty bad.
皮西装 皮西装着实太糟糕了
Thank you for having me to your nana's.
多谢你带我来你曾奶奶的聚会
Are you kidding me? You're my best friend. We're family.
你在开什么玩笑? 你可是我最好的朋友 我们是一家人
Oh, my God.
噢 天哪
- This is gluten-free. Try a taste.  - Hm?
- 这是无谷蛋白的 尝一下吧  - 啥?
Why the heck are you two sitting over here all by yourselves?
见鬼了 你们两个人怎么独自坐在这?
You're not gonna make me any great-grandbabies this way.
你这样可不能给我生出个重孙子来
It is a family gathering, Nana.
这是个家庭聚会呀 奶奶
I don't think you want us making any great-grandbabies.
我不觉得你想让我们生什么重孙子
To be fair, I have already provided you with a wonderful great-grandchild.
说句实在话 我已经给你们一个棒极了的重孙子
Yeah, but that doesn't count because you screwed it all up.
是呀 但是那不算数因为你把一切都搞砸了
- Ouch.  - Come on, Lil.
- 噢  - 过来吧 莉尔
Let's show these kids how it's done, huh?
让这些孩子看看那是怎么做的 好吧?
- Heh, heh. See?  - Ciao.
- 嘿 嘿 看见没?  - 再见
It's kind of gross when they kiss.
他们接吻的时候真有点粗犷
God, I love that kid.
天哪 我真喜欢那个孩子
What's going on?
发生什么事了?
Hey, Mr. Deep-ln-Thought. You wanna talk about it?
嘿 "沉思"先生 要聊聊这个吗?
I was just... That kind of thing's lovely, isn't it?
我只是在... 那看上去真不错 不是吗?
- It's really lovely.  - What's lovely?
- 真的很不错  - 什么东西很不错?
I love the way they look into each other's eyes like that.
我喜欢他们那样互相注视着对方的样子
I'm pretty sure that's the cataracts.
我很确定那是白内障
Have you... Okay. You asked me a serious question, didn't you?
你有没有... 好吧 你问了我一个很严肃的问题 不是吗?
- Yeah. Yeah.  - Right. So do you want a serious answer?
- 嗯 是的  - 好吧 那么你想要个严肃的答案了?
- Yeah. Put the cake down?  - Please.
- 是吧 把蛋糕先放下?  - 好的
- Okay.  - Thank you.
- 好吧  - 多谢了
Cake is down. Talk to me.
蛋糕放下了 跟我说说吧
- Well, no, seriously, man chat. Okay?  - Okay.
- 好了 严肃点 这是男人间的对话 行吗?  - 当然可以
Man to man.
男人对男人间的交谈
I trust you. I know you'd do anything for me.
我信任你 我知道你会为我做任何事情
- Yeah.  - You would take a bullet for me.
- 是的  - 你会为我挡子弹
I would for you as well, you know that. Right?
我也会为你这么做的 你懂的 对吧?
- Can you imagine all of that?  - Yes.
- 你能想象到那个场景吗?  - 可以
Can you imagine what that would be like to share with a woman?
你能想象到和一个女人分享那一切是什么感觉吗?
No.
不行
Okay.
可以的
No.
不可以
Thank you.
谢了
All right, Joe, Steven, you're up.
好了 乔 史蒂夫 该你们了
- All right, Joe. Good luck, son.  - Let's go to war.
- 好了 乔 好运 我的儿子  - 开始战斗了
That's it. Now you feint. Nice feint.
就是这样 现在假装攻击 干得好
- Hit.  - Oh, nice. Get on him. Oh!
- 打他  - 噢 打得不错 骑到他身上 噢!
Down he goes. Ground and pound him.
他倒下了 按倒地上打他
Get on him. Ground and pound. Ground and pound.
到他身上去 近身打他 猛击他
- Uh...  - Keep it going. Hammerfist him.
- 额...  - 继续吧 重拳出击
Right there, that's it. Hit it. He's giving you his back.
就是那 就打那里 他要跟你投降了
- Rear naked choke.  - I give. I give.
- 绞在一起了  - 我投降 我投降了
Yes. He's tapping. He's out. Booyah!
好了 他捶地了 他出局了 哇哦!
See what I mean? That's how it works, boy.
明白我的意思了吧 就是这么做的 孩子
See that? I pwned him, didn't I?
看见没? 我打败他了 对吧?
- Good. You okay?  - Sure did, son.
- 很好 你还好吧?  - 你当然打败他了 儿子
Ha, ha!
哈哈!
- That's how you kill him.  - What are you doing here?
- 你就是那样打败他的  - 你在这干嘛?
Well, I had a bit of time off and I thought I'd come hang with my homey.
好了 我休息一段时间 我觉得我该来享受下家庭的温暖
I got creamed.
我被痛扁了
No, you didn't, that's just a matter of opinion.
不 你没有 这事儿你得这么看
What do you know about fighting?
你懂搏击吗?
You're just a travel agent.
你只是个旅行社的
I know enough to know that he who hesitates...
我很清楚的知道那些犹豫不决的人...
Pain?
疼吧?
That's just weakness leaving the body.
那只是你的虚弱离开了你的身体
Oh, Dad.
喔 老爸
Joe. Joe, Joe.
乔 乔 乔
- Come on, boys.  - Mom, did you see me win today?
- 过来 孩子们  - 妈妈 你今天看到我赢了吗?
On the mat? That's amazing.
在那个垫子上? 真是令人惊讶
- Hey, guys.  - Hey.
- 嘿 伙计们  - 嘿
- Hey, bud.  - Hi.
- 嘿 伙计  - 嗨
- Hey, Tuck.  - Hey, how you doing?
- 嘿 塔克  - 你最近怎么样?
Didn't know you were in town.
都不知道你来镇子上了
Got a couple days off so I thought I'd come see Joe.
休假几天所以我觉得我该来看看乔
You're the only travel agent I've ever met who actually travels for his job.
你是我见过的唯一一个为自己工作到处旅行的旅行代理商
Yeah.
是的
Um, so I was thinking that maybe, um...
额 我在想也许 嗯...
Maybe you, me and Joe, we could all go out together...
也许你和乔还有我 我们可以一起出去
you know, as a family, maybe get something to eat.
你懂的 作为一个家庭 也许可以去吃点东西
Have a meal. I think that would be really, really good.
吃顿饭 我觉得那会非常不错的
I have a date tonight, Tuck.
我今晚有个约会 塔克
So maybe some other time.
那么也许换个时间吧
Sure. That's great. Good. That's good.
当然了 很好 是的 很好
Bye, Joe.
再见了 乔
So good.
真不错
Do you believe it?
你们相信吗?
This is simply extraordinary.
这简直是奇特万分
What an amazing end to this first half of play.
上半场的惊人结局
Are you looking for someone to start a life with?
你正在寻找和你一起生活的人吗?
Would you rather spend your time with your soul mate than at work?
你更愿意和你的灵魂伴侣呆在一起还是花时间去工作?
With over 6 million eligible singles...
我们拥有600万以上合适的单身人群...
It's Fate.net will help you find that special person.
命运网将帮助你找到那个特殊的人
Find your soul mate with just one click. Log on today...
点击一下即可找到你的灵魂伴侣 今日登陆...
- and take our 15-minute test...  - Shh! Let me watch.
- 进行我们15分钟的测试...  - 嘘 让我看看
and open the door to your new love life.
打开通向你崭新爱情生活的门吧
No more lonely nights.
不再有寂寞的夜晚
No more empty mornings.
不再有空虚的早晨
Give yourself the gift of love.
给你自己送上爱的礼物吧
You deserve it. It's Fate.net. What have you got to lose?
你值得拥有 快来命运网 你又会损失什么呢?
That's just so sad.
太难过了
- Good morning, Ella.  - Good morning.
- 早上好 艾拉  - 早上好
- Here she comes. Here she comes.  - Hi, there.
- 她来了 她来了  - 嗨 你好
- Looking good, boss.  - What?
- 看上去不错呀 老板  - 什么?
- Hi, Paul.  - What? Nothing.
- 嗨 保罗  - 什么? 没事
- Good morning, Hudson.  - I'm down, girl.
- 早上好 哈德森  - 我有点失落呀 丫头
I'm down too.
我也是
Emily. What am I down with?
艾米丽 我有什么不对劲的地方?
Oh, my goodness. It's a...
噢 我的天哪 是一个...
Your... Check your desktop.
你的... 查收下你的电脑吧
男孩们  来抱个美人归吧！
Oh, crap.
喔 废话
- Hi.  - Bi-curious? Skinny-dipping?
- 嗨  - 对双性恋感到好奇? 裸泳?
Rollerblading? I mean, what is this, 1994?
滑旱冰? 我是说 这是什么 1994年?
You looked adorable in those shorts. Men are gonna respond to that camel toe.
你穿那条短裤很可爱 男人会对你那样子起反应的
I'm gonna kill you, Trish.
我要杀了你 翠西
Uh, how about "thank you" ?
额 说句"谢谢"就好了
My office thinks I clean my house in a naughty nurse costume.
我的同事都认为我穿着不规矩的护士服在打扫房子
That's fine. That means you're open to role-playing.
很好呀 那就表示你对角色扮演还是可以接受的
We're trying to cast a wide net. We don't know what guys you like.
我们要撒大网啊 谁知道你喜欢什么样的男人
You've got me in a keg stand looking for a serious relationship.
你拿我玩"倒立一醉方休"的照片去相亲
- I don't even know what that means.  - It means you're flexible.
- 那是什么意思  - 意思是你很灵活
Guys wanna know that you're flexible and good at gymnastics.
男人都想知道 你很灵活也擅长体操
No, no, that's Mommy's special milk, okay?
不 不行 那是妈妈的特殊牛奶 好吗?
Just get me off this thing. How do I cancel it?
让我摆脱这个东西就行了 我怎么才能删掉它?
You're not canceling it. I'm in charge of that. You're not canceling it. Sorry.
你删不掉的 我才能编辑那些 你是删不掉的 抱歉啦
Wait a second. Who is that?
等一下 那是谁?
Oh, my God. He's cute.
噢 天哪 他真可爱
Let me get this straight. You put your personal, private details...
我直说了啊 你把你私人详细的资料...
- On a very public website?  - Yes.
- 放在了一个公共网站上?  - 是的
- Are you insane?  - No.
- 你疯了吗?  - 没有
- Where you taking her?  - Don't do that to me.
- 你要带她去哪?  - 不要这么对我
- Taking her to the Blarney Stone.  - I like the jukebox.
- 带她去巧言石呀  - 我喜欢自动点唱机
- You're such a cheeseball.  - What?
- 你真讨打  - 什么?
You're gonna go on this date and I'm gonna go with you.
你要去约会 我也会和你一起去
- No, you're not.  - Yes, I am.
- 不行 你不能去  - 不 我就要去
I'm scared. You haven't done this in a long time.
我很担心 你很久没这么做了
This girl could be all sorts of crazy.
这个女孩可能是疯的
And, besides, half those girls pee standing up, Tuck.
而且 半数那样的女孩都是站着小便的 塔克
The other half are on one of our watch lists.
另一半的女孩都在我们的监视名单上
- It's a date.  - Look, lucky for you, I'm free tonight.
- 那是个约会  - 听着 你走运了 我今晚休息
And I'm gonna bring the binoculars, the hand cream...
我会带来望远镜和润手霜...
keep a hundred-yard radius. It'll be sweet stuff.
保持一百码的距离 那都会是很好的材料
No, you can't bring the binoculars. You're not watching my date.
不行 你不能带望远镜 你可不能监视我的约会
I need a little privacy.
我需要一点隐私
I'll be around the corner on ringtone. I'll be at the video store.
铃声一响我就会过来 我就在音像店里
One ring means you need an extraction, two, a cleaner, three, I can get home.
响一声说明你需要脱身 响两声说明需要清洁工 三声我就可以回家了
- Two hundred yards.  - Sold.
- 离我两百码  - 就这么定了
Tuck? Are you Tuck?
塔克吗? 你是塔克吗?
Hi. I'm Lauren.
嗨 我是劳伦
Oh, my gosh. Hello. How are you.
哦 我的天啊 嗨 你好啊
Very nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你
You too. Um....
我也是 嗯...
Please, sit. Please, sorry. Yeah.
请坐 不好意思 快请坐
Wow, it's like... You are really, really beautiful.
哇哦 这... 你真是十分非常太漂亮了
Could you say that a few more times, because your voice is amazing.
你能多说几遍吗 你声音听起来太迷人了
I feel like I need to apologize again for that bizarre profile.
我真的不好意思我那份奇怪的个人档案
- No, no, no.  - My friend, Trish, is....
- 不用 不用  - 是我朋友 翠西...
Oh, no. Don't be silly. I think everybody should have a friend who's a spaz.
不用 别傻了 我觉得每个人身边总有几个二货的
- I think I'm going to have to kill her.  - Well, actually...
- 我觉得我还是杀了她比较好  - 这样的话...
- I might be able to help you.  - I'm kidding.
- 我可能帮得上忙  - 我是说笑的
- So am I.  - Love...
- 我也是  - 爱情...
is the only thing that can save this poor creature.
是唯一能拯救这个卑微的生命的东西了
And I am going to convince him that he is loved...
而我就算用尽我的余生...
even at the cost of my own life.
也要让他明白 他已经恋爱了
No matter what you hear in there, no matter how cruelly I beg you...
不管你听到里面发出什么声音 不管我多么努力地哀求
- no matter how terribly I may scream...  - Hi.
- 不管我的尖叫多么吓人...  - 嗨
do not open this door or you will undo everything I've worked for.
千万别打开那扇门 不然我做的一切都会因你而前功尽弃
Good for you, pal.
干得好 伙计
So tell me one thing that's not on your profile.
那跟我说件你档案上没有的事吧
Um...
嗯...
I have a son.
我有个儿子
- Oh, you do?  - Yeah. He's called Joe.
- 哦 你有儿子了?  - 是的 他叫乔
He's 7 and he's really lovely. Really lovely.
他7岁了 很可爱 很可爱的小孩子
And his mom?
那他妈妈呢?
Couldn't work.
我们合不来
How about you?
那你呢?
- No kids that I know of.  - Okay.
- 据我所知 还没有孩子  - 好的
And no ex-wives.
也没前妻什么的
- I have a very important question to ask.  - Good. Go on.
- 我有个很重要的问题要问  - 好的 问吧
Have you ever been or do you ever plan on being a serial killer?
你曾经或者计划要做杀人狂吗?
Well, I mean, it's... You gotta keep your options open.
我想说 这... 未来什么可能性都是有的
- But, no.  - Okay, good answer.
- 但是 没打算  - 哦 答得好
So you've never killed anybody with your bare hands.
所以你没空手杀过人咯
Not this week.
起码这周没有
Great.
好极了
- Lauren, you're incredible.  - You're not so bad yourself.
- 劳伦 你太正了  - 你也不差啊
All right, I'm gonna go and rent a movie and take a cold shower.
好了 我要去租个电影 洗个冷水澡
- I will too.  - Okay.
- 我也差不多  - 好的
- And wait for your call for the next...  - Five minutes?
- 然后就坐等你的电话啦...  - 等五分钟够吗?
This is where it all started.
一切就这么开始了
Yes, I was standing over there by that desk.
没错 我站在那书桌的旁边
No, you were sitting in the chair. And suddenly, you started walking toward me.
不对 你是坐在椅子上的 而突然 你向我走来
Very slowly. Very slowly.
慢慢的 慢慢的
I could count every step.
我都能数出你的步调了
And when you're walking towards me very slowly...
当你这么慢地向我走来的时候...
I thought, What's the matter with him? Can't he walk faster?
我在想 他这是怎么了? 他就不能走快一点吗?
- Oh, I'm so sorry.  - Oh, I'm sorry. You take it.
- 哦 不好意思  - 哦 不好意思 还是你拿吧
- No, no, no, that's okay. You take it.  - Sure?
- 没事 没关系的 给你吧  - 你确定吗?
You're not gonna like it. Twist ending. You'll see it coming a mile away.
实话说吧 你不会喜欢这电影的 反转的结局 你看了一半就搞清楚了
- And how would you know what I like?  - I know movies. And women.
- 你怎么知道我会喜欢什么的?  - 我懂电影 还懂女人
- Really?  - Mm-hm.
- 真的?  - 嗯哼
Okay.
好吧
Well, why don't you tell me what I want?
那你告诉我 我想要的是什么?
- "The Lady Vanishes"? Why is that?  - Mm-hm.
- "贵妇失踪案"? 为什么是这部呢?  - 嗯哼
Well, firstly, you can never go wrong with Hitchcock. Ever.
首先 你选希区柯克的电影是绝对不会错的 绝对的
It's got comedy, drama, romance, it's a thriller.
里面内集喜剧 话剧 浪漫剧的元素 本身是部惊悚片
It's classy, but not stuffy.
很经典 但不无聊
A little obscure, so if you haven't seen it, you'll thank me for introducing you to it.
但名气没那么大 所以如果你没看过的话 你看完会庆幸我把它介绍给你的
If you have, you'll know what a good choice it was.
如果你看过了 你就知道选这本电影不会错的
- Well, I have seen it.  - Mm-hm.
- 其实我看过了  - 嗯哼
- And it is a really good choice.  - Mm.
- 选这本电影是不错  - 嗯
However, not as good as "Rebecca", "Notorious", "Vertigo"...
但比不上"蝴蝶梦" "谍网情鸳" "迷魂记"...
or pretty much any of his films from 1960 to 1972.
可以说他1960到1972年每本电影都比这个要强
In fact, it's sort of a second-tier title.
老实说 这就只能算个二流的题材
A second...
二流...
- You know what? Scratch...  - Look, I see you surveying the prospects.
- 你知道吗? 小野猫...  - 听着 我知道你在找猎艳的对象
That one over there in foreign? Too much angst.
那边那个外国来的? 太怨妇状了
This one in the sweater set, picking out animated movies?
这个穿毛衣的 在选动画片的那个?
That girl will have your children named before breakfast.
那女孩明早就会吵着要你负责的
The problem is, no one looks like a clean getaway.
问题就在于这里每个女人 似乎都不能让人轻易脱身
I get it. You come in here looking for a girl renting a movie.
我懂的 你来这里找个租电影的女孩
Clearly, she doesn't have a date for the night. We're easy targets.
很明显 她晚上肯定没有约会 这样的女人就容易下手
You look like the guy interested in a one-day rental...
你看起来就像是喜欢搞一夜情的
If you know what I mean, if you knew anything about women...
如果你知道我在说什么的话 如果你懂一点点女人的话...
or anything about me, I'm perfectly capable of choosing my own movies.
对我有点了解的话 我自己选电影是完全没问题的
But thanks.
但还是谢谢选我啦
Happy hunting.
猎艳愉快啊
Hm.
嗯
So, sir, you want me to hack into a video store database?
大哥 你是想让我黑进一个租录像的数据库啊?
- It's for the Heinrich case.  - Searching database.
- 这事关海因里希案件  - 搜索数据库
All right, keep on scrolling.
好的 继续翻下去
Wait. Stop. Scroll back.
等等 停住 倒回去
That's her.
就是她
Sir, how is this girl connected to Heinrich?
大哥 这个女的怎么会和海因里希案子有关系呢?
That's G-4 classified.
这是G-4级的机密
Hello, everybody, I'm Lauren Scott. Thank you so much for being here today.
大家好 我是劳伦・斯科特 谢谢大家今天能来这里
Good morning, Lauren.
早上好 劳伦
We're here today to talk about grills. Does anybody have any first impressions?
今天我们要谈谈这个烧烤架 大家对此有什么第一印象如何?
I like the rotisserie feature.
我喜欢它带的旋转功能
Perfect. That's very helpful.
好极了 很有价值
I don't think it heated up fast enough.
我觉得它可能热起来不够快
Like something was wrong with the motor, maybe the spark was dead.
或许加热器出问题了 或者火花塞塞住了
Actually, sir, there's nothing wrong with the spark.
这位先生 其实火花塞没什么问题
Some people think grills just burst into flames at the slightest touch.
有些人觉得烤箱就应该是一下子加热到高温的
It doesn't work like that.
但事实不是这个样子的
Does anybody have any useful opinions?
其他人还有什么好的意见建议吗?
- I thought the lid was hard to handle.  - Mm-hm.
- 我觉得那盖子用起来很不方便  - 好的
Ugh... The lids, what a pain, right?
额... 那盖子 烦死人了 不是吗?
I just felt the whole thing to be a bit stiff, uptight, not really user-friendly.
我就觉得那东西硬邦邦的 没创意 一点不为用户着想
I think it depends on the user.
我觉得这和用的人有关
It so happens I have a lot of experience with grills.
但碰巧我对烧烤架还是很有经验的
I'm something of a grill master.
我算是个烧烤大师吧
Uh, this is a sophisticated grill. I am not sure you've dealt with one of those before.
嗯 这是个很高端的烤架 我觉得你之前没用过这类型的
Or maybe a grill like this is just so scared of being burned...
或者这种烤架只是担心被烧到
It stays on simmer and never really heats up all the way.
只能慢火小煮 从来受不了大火的加热
- Don't touch my grill.  - I don't think this can handle a guy like me.
- 不准碰我的烤架  - 我觉得它是禁不起我折腾的
- I think it could.  - Really?
- 我觉得它可以的  - 真的吗?
- Easily.  - Prove it. 8 p.m. Barcelona. Tomorrow.
- 小意思  - 事实说话 明天巴塞罗那酒吧 晚8点
I don't think so.
想都别想
I guess I could stick around a little longer, talk about grills.
那我就再呆一会儿好了 聊聊烤架
Charcoal or gas, number 19, what do you think?
烤炭啊 煤气啊 19号 你觉得怎么样?
If I say yes, will you leave? This is my job.
如果我答应 你就走嘛? 我这可是在工作
- Eight p.m. tomorrow.  - Fine.
- 明天晚上八点  - 好的
- Fine.  - Fine.
- 好极了  - 好的
You smell nice.
你真好闻
Bye.
拜啦
What were you doing on the computer? Porn?
你在电脑上做什么呢? 下黄片吗?
- I have a photograph of my girl.  - I was doing the same thing.
- 在看我女朋友的照片  - 我也在做一样的事情
A background check. I don't know if that's creepy or romantic.
我在调查我女朋友的背景资料 我都不知道该说你变态呢 还是浪漫呢
"Cromantic." I do it all the time. Wanna see?
就算变态的浪漫好了 我经常干的 你要看她的照片嘛?
- Yeah, sure. Wanna see her?  - Yeah.
- 当然要啦 你要看她的嘛?  - 好啊
I bet yours has got antlers and howls.
我打赌你那个肯定长得稀奇古怪的
She does, but she's incredibly attractive with them.
就算是吧 但她也稀奇古怪得迷死人了
- She's a 10.  - Go on three.
- 她可是10分女哦  - 那数到三一起看
- One, two, three and go? All right.  - Yeah.
- 一 二 三然后一起看? 好的  - 没问题
- Okay. I'll sound off.  - Okay.
- 好的 那我来报数  - 好的
- One...  - One.
- 一...  - 一
two... three.
二... 三
- That's, uh, Lauren S...  - Lauren? Lauren Scott?
- 嗯 那是劳伦・斯...  - 这不是劳伦吗? 劳伦・斯科特?
Scott...
是斯科特...
That's the girl from the video store? Right around the corner from the bar.
那个就是你说的录像店遇到的女人? 那地方就在你那酒吧的转角
Oh, wow. Um....
哦 哇哦 嗯...
- I had no idea.  - Of course. How could you know that?
- 我真的不知道的  - 不知道了 你怎么会想到?
Did she, ahem, actually say she wanted to go out on a date with you, though?
哦 但她...真的说想和你出去约会吗?
You know what? I'm gonna make this really easy. I'm gonna bow out. You date her.
你知道怎么着? 我就快刀斩乱麻了 我退出好了 你去约她
Hang on. Did she say she wanted to go out with you?
等等 等等 她说了她想和你出去约会?
It doesn't matter. I love you. You're my best friend.
这不重要了 我在乎你的 你是我最好的朋友
- Yeah.  - You go date her.
- 好吧  - 你去约她好了
Yeah, if I got in the picture, it wouldn't be fair.
好了 如果我插一脚的话 对你就太不公平了
Well, I'm sorry. What does that mean?
哦 不好意思 你说这话什么意思?
- What does that mean?  - I mean, come on, man...
- 这话什么意思?  - 拜托 伙计 我是说...
you're not out there as much as I am.
你那方面就没有那么好了
And like anything...
就像说的那样...
- practice makes, uh...  - Perfect?
- 熟能生 嗯...  - 熟能生巧?
- No, no, no.  - You're perfect?
- 不是 不是  - 你已经完美了咯?
Maybe not perfect, but... damn near close...
也许不算完美 但... 但也差不多那样子了...
Wow.
哇哦
- to perfect.  - You believe that as well?
- 算完美了  - 你自己也是这么觉得的?
- You don't have to bow out because of me.  - I don't?
- 你不用为了我退出的  - 我不用退出?
I'm not concerned that she's gonna fall in love with you, pal.
我完全不用担心她会喜欢上你 伙计
- How very nice of you. Thank you.  - You are welcome.
- 你真是太看得起我了 谢谢了  - 不用谢
So do your thing.
所以就尽管来吧
Whatever that is.
什么手段都使出来吧
And, um...
呃...
Just let her decide.
就让她来做决定吧
- Sure.  - Yeah.
- 好的  - 没问题
Yeah.
好的
While we're at it, why don't we put ground rules in as well?
既然我们说定了 为什么不定一点规矩呢?
- I think we should.  - Number one, I don't think...
- 我也这么觉得  - 第一点 我觉得...
we should tell we know each other. Two, stay out of each other's way.
我们不应该告诉她我们认识 第二 互相之间不许插手
Three. Yeah. No hanky-panky, no hanky-panky.
第三 没错 不许偷偷摸摸 鬼头鬼脑的
God, you have not dated in a long time, have you?
天啊 你很长时间没约会了 是吧?
And if this ever starts to affect our friendship...
而且如果这影响到我们之间朋友关系的话...
- Which it won't.  - which it won't...
- 不太可能的  - 虽然不太可能...
- then we walk away.  - Done.
- 但我们也要马上抽身出来  - 同意
- So, then, we have... We have...  - We have a gentleman's agreement.
- 那我们有... 我们有了...  - 我们有君子协定了
- A gentleman's agreement. We do.  - May the best man win.
- 君子协定 的确如此  - 愿最好的那个获胜
The best man for her.
对她最好的人
- For her.  - For the lady.
- 是对她  - 对这位女士
For the lady, for her, the best man for her.
是对她的 对她最好的人
中央情报局外勤办公室
伦敦・英国
萨 维 尔 街
Oh! Uh...
哦! 嗯...
Forgive me, Sir. You startled me.
请原谅我 先生吓到我了
I understand you're Savile Row's finest.
我知道你是萨维尔街上最好的裁缝
We do our best, sir.
我们尽力让自己最好 先生
In that case, I'd like to have a suit in this fabric.
这样的话 我想要用这布料做件衣服
Ah, South American vicuna. An excellent choice indeed.
啊 南美的骆马毛 的确是个不错的选择
One thing with my suits, I like to know they are one of a kind.
我这件衣服的话 我希望它是独一无二的
I wouldn't want anyone wearing the same suit.
我不想有其他人也穿同样的衣服
I'm sure you understand that. Of course, sir. With this fabric and color...
我肯定你懂的 当然啦 先生 用这种特定颜色和面料...
I only made one other, and that was for a gentleman who lives quite far away.
我另外就只做过一件 那是家住离这里很远的一个先生定做的
How far exactly?
确切地说是多远?
Los Angeles.
在洛杉矶
Have you any reason to go there soon?
你最近有什么事要去那里吗?
I do now.
现在我有了
Hello. Sorry, I'm not in. Please leave a message after the tone.
喂 抱歉我暂时无法接通 请留言
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
我会尽快给你回电
Tuck, Tuck.
塔克 塔克
Where are you, man? Five o'clock.
你在哪里呢 伙计? 已经五点了
CHiPs marathon about to start, I got new sticks for "Rock Band."
摇滚时间到 我弄到了上好的鼓槌哟
Call me.
打回给我啊
- My God, I love these places.  - I thought you might.
- 我的天啊 我爱死这地方了  - 我就觉得你会喜欢的
We're not gonna leave until we've spent our tokens.
不用完所有的钱币 我们就不离开了
Hello. I'm sorry, I'm not in. Please leave a message after the tone.
喂 抱歉我暂时无法接通 请留言
Get back to you as soon as possible.
我会尽快打给你的
Dude, where are you?
大哥 你到哪里去啦?
Oh!
哦!
Hey, man, uh, it's about 5:43. Uh...
嘿 伙计 现在快5:43了 啊...
So whatever, man, just hanging out, watching the thing.
不管做什么 就不去逛逛 看看球什么的
Are you...? Maybe your phone's turned off or something.
你是在...? 也许你电话关机了什么的
But check it to make... Clearly, you can't check it and see if it...
但查一下打回... 很明显 关机的话 你就查不到了...
Whatever. Call me.
不管了 打给我就行
So the great air hockey cheats, that is.
桌上冰球蛮厉害吗 很厉害吗
I'm available for lessons anytime.
想报仇的话 随时来找我啊
But only for you.
但只和你打
There's something else I wanna show you.
我还想给你看其他东西
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
我会尽快打给你的
Hey, man, so, uh, I'm a little worried. I don't know if, um...
嘿 伙计 我有点担心了 我不知道你...
You haven't returned my calls for, like, a long time now, like an hour.
你好像很久没回我电话了 嗯... 快一个小时了
So, uh, just give me a call if you're okay, okay?
所以你没事的话就给我打个电话吧 好吗?
Okay. I've said "okay" now, like, five times.
好吗 我开始自言自语了
Give me a call. Oka...
给我打个电话 好...
Okay, where are we going?
我们要去哪里?
- There are lions in here.  - No.
- 有狮子在那里  - 别啊
- Yes.  - Are you serious?
- 有的  - 你说真的吗?
Okay. Open them.
好了 睁开眼吧
Wow, it's so beautiful.
哇哦 太漂亮了
Come on.
来吧
We're going up there?
我们要到上面去?
- You're gonna catch me, right?  - Yeah.
- 你会接住我的 对吗?  - 当然啦
- Promise?  - Absolutely.
- 你保证?  - 妥妥的
- Okay.  - One...
- 好吧  - 一...
Yeah.
好的
two...
二...
three.
三
There you go.
就是这样
Oh, my gosh.
哦 我的天啊
- Okay, okay.  - Right.
- 好的 好的  - 没骗你吧
- What was that?  - I'm sorry, I lost my grip.
- 刚刚怎么回事?  - 是我的错 我没抓紧
You did that on purpose.
你是故意的
Uh... Maybe I did.
嗯... 也许是吧
I think you did.
我觉得你是故意的
Well, sometimes falling is the best part.
有时候下落才是最美好的部分
Come on.
快点
- Yeah.  - I'm coming.
- 好的  - 我来了啊
I am so horny.
我就是饥渴
Hold on.
等一下
- Hello.  - Hey, it's me. Can you talk?
- 喂  - 喂 是我 我们能聊聊吗?
- Yeah, what's up?  - It's... I don't know.
- 能啊 怎么了?  - 是... 我不知道
I feel weird about dating two guys at once.
我觉得同时和两个人约会好奇怪啊
Are you serious? Stop feel bad about dating two guys.
真的假的? 约两个人有什么好奇怪的...
This is good, okay? You gotta go out there and live a life...
这是好现象 懂吗? 你就是要出去享受生活
for women like me who can't...
但像我这样的女人就不行了...
who have to have sex with the same guy every Wednesday night at 9:00...
我就只能每周三晚9点跟同一个男人混在一起
- while we're eating Cheetos.  - That's kind of awesome.
- 而且我们在吃奇多  - 感觉超赞的样子
It is awesome.
这的确赞啊
For women everywhere.
为了天下的女人
That's the spirit. Do it. And Bob's super horny, I gotta go.
就是这样子 去吧 鲍勃饥渴死了 我要挂了
Okay. Bye.
好的 拜拜
Okay. For women everywhere. I love it, I love it, I love it.
对的 为天下的女人 我爱它 爱它 爱死它
Tuck.
塔克
Where's your partner?
你搭档呢?
- Oh, he went out on a date.  - Of course he did.
- 哦 他出去约会了  - 那当然的了
The guy's an assassin, slays everything he sets his sights on, right?
那家伙就是个杀手 见人杀人 见佛杀佛 没说错吧?
We got a positive lock on that license plate.
我们已经锁定了那辆车
- Do you want us to put it up?  - Yes.
- 你要我连上吗?  - 好的
No. Actually, no, don't.
不用 还是不用了
- Yeah, go on. If you would, thanks, yeah.  - Okay.
- 好吧 就这样 你能连上的话 连上吧 谢谢了  - 好的
No. No, we can't.
不行 我们不能这样
Yeah. You gotta do it now. Go on.
好吧 你还是做吧 继续吧
- I'm here now.  - Okay.
- 我看着就行了  - 好的
Wow.
哇哦
- I wasn't sure if you were gonna show.  - I told you I could handle it.
- 我没想到你会来的  - 说了这对我小意思的啊
We'll see. Come on.
到时候看吧 快点
- Oh, I don't wanna lose my spot.  - Don't worry about it.
- 哦 那是我排的队啊  - 不用管它了
After you.
你先请
Go ahead.
请进
Let them through.
让他们进去
- Good to see you, buddy.  - How you doing?
- 见到你真高兴 哥们  - 你还好吗?
You'll gonna love this place, I swear. Hey, Ciera. How are you?
我发誓你肯定会喜欢这个地方的 你好 西拉 你好吗?
I think you're enjoying yourself. You just have to loosen up. Get off the simmer.
我想你会尽兴的 你只要放松肌肉 逐步释放激情
Nathaniel.
纳萨尼尔
What's up, baby? How you been?
怎么样 老兄? 近来可好?'
Look at you. Oh!
瞧瞧你 哦!
You are shining like a bright light.
你真是光彩照人
You guys are here? Come on.
你们也在呢? 真巧啊
All right, I gotta go say hi to the DJ. He knows me.
好了 我们得去和调音师打个招呼 他是我朋友
Come on. Come on in. Come on. Come on.
快 进来吧 来吧 快过来
What's up?
你好?
After you, my lady.
您先请 我的女士
'85 Veuve, Sammy.
萨米 给我一瓶85年的凯歌香槟
Hey. Where are you going?
嘿 你去哪?
- Where are you going? We just got here.  - You know what?
- 你去哪? 我们才刚来  - 你知道吗?
- I'm not the girl for you.  - Oh, come on, just...
- 我不适合你  - 哦 拜托 只是...
Come inside for a minute, we'll have a good time.
进去待会儿 我们会玩得很开心的
It's really okay. I've done this.
真的没必要了 我已经尝试过了
I was a gymnast back in high school, my best event was the keg stand.
高中时我是名体操员 拿手好戏就是"倒立一醉方休"
- You're a gymnast?  - Unbelievable.
- 你是体操运动员?  - 难以置信
What's about the question. You said you were a gymnast, I asked a question.
那有什么关系 你说你是名体操运动员 而我 不过跟你确认一下
That's exactly why I'm walking away.
因为 这就是我离开的原因
Because you're uptight and don't know how to have good time?
因为你太紧张 而且不知如何从中取乐?
You have the emotional intelligence of a 15-year-old boy.
你的情商只有15岁
You think I'd be interested in going out with you or going back up in the club?
你觉得我会有兴趣和你约会或者跟你回酒吧吗?
- I don't think so.  - Thank you, judgmental princess.
- 我想我不会  - 谢你啊 评头论足小姐
- Can we just call it a night?  - Can we please call it a night?
- 我们能到此为止?  - 请问我们能到此为止吗?
- Good night.  - Sayonara.
- 再见  - 再见
- Have fun.  - Ciao. Go back to the retirement village.
- 玩得开心  - 回你的疗养院吧
Of course I do.
当然啦
Oh, my God. This is not happening.
哦 天娜 不能这么巧吧
Come back here. Wait, wait, wait.
回来 等等 等等 等一下
- Just kiss me.  - What? Absolutely not.
- 吻我  - 什么? 没门
- I'm serious.  - Why would I? No.
- 我说真的  - 为什么
- Just kiss me right now.  - I'm not gonna kiss you. You're bipolar.
- 现在就吻我  - 我才不吻 你有双重人格
- Stop.  - Oh.
- 住手  - 哦
Lauren. Uh....
劳伦 呃...
Lauren, hey.
劳伦 嘿
- There you are.  - Oh. Oh, Steve.
- 你在这呢  - 哦 哦 史蒂文
Oh, my God, that is so funny running into you again. That's so funny.
哦 天呐 真有意思又碰上你了 太巧了
Um.... This is my boyfriend, FDR.
嗯... 这是我男朋友富兰克林
Huh.
哈
He, uh... He's the surgeon that we were talking about.
他 呃... 他就是以前我给你提到过的那个外科医生
- Huh.  - Yeah.
- 嗯  - 是的
Neurosurgeon. I'm the department head at the children's hospital.
神经外科医生 我是儿童医院的部门主任
Wow, that's amazing.
喔 你太了不起了
- He is. He's really amazing.  - Stop it.
- 是啊 他的确很棒  - 别这样说
- Amazing?  - I don't know what makes me happier.
- 很棒吗?  - 我不知道还有什么能让我更幸福
Smile on a child's face or waking up next to you every morning.
孩子们天真无邪的笑容 还是每天早晨和你相拥醒来
- I love you.  - I love you. I love you too. That's so funny.
- 我爱你  - 我爱你 我也爱你 真有趣
Jinx. Ha-ha-ha.
坏蛋 哈哈哈
- We're really happy.  - Yeah, we are.
- 我们真的很幸福  - 是啊 那还用说
- Yeah.  - Who wouldn't be happy with a girl like this?
- 是啊  - 有你这样的女孩相伴还有有谁不幸福呢?
Look at her, She's got everything.
看看她 真是完美无瑕
- She got the beauty, style, grace.  - He's so sweet to me.
- 她漂亮 时尚 而又优雅  - 他总是对我这么体贴
- Did you know she was a gymnast in high school?  - No, I didn't know.
- 你知道她高中时是体操运动员吗?  - 不 我不知道
- Didn't think so.  - Yeah.
- 想不到吧  - 是啊
He likes it.
他喜欢我这点
- Frisky, I love it.  - Yeah.
- 真调皮 我喜欢  - 我知道
- Can you do that thing on the high bar?  - Yeah. I think... I think we should get going.
- 你能在高杆上做那事吗?  - 我想... 我想我们该走了
- Stan, it was such a pleasure. We gotta go.  - I mean, it's Steve, but that's cool.
- 史丹 认识你真高兴 我们也得走了  - 我叫史蒂夫 不过 史丹听着也很不错
- Great meeting you.  - Steve, yeah. Whatever
- 很高兴认识你  - 史蒂夫 当然 无所谓啦
Really nice meeting you.
能认识你真是太高兴了
- Really nice meeting you?  - Sweetheart,it was a pleasure.
- 真的很高兴认识你?  - 甜心 听到你这么说真是太荣幸了
Oh, look at that. A little kiss on the hand there.
哦 快看呐 还吻手礼
- That's sweet.  - You are so lucky.
- 真体贴  - 你太幸运了
- I know.  - Yeah.
- 我知道  - 嗯
- Bye.  - Bye now, guys.
- 再见  - 再见 各位
- Yeah.  - See you. Have fun, Simon.
- 再见  - 再见 玩得开心 西蒙
- It's Steve.  - Okay. Thank you so much.
- 我叫史蒂夫  - 好了 太谢谢你了
What did you say? This ear's a little deaf.
你刚说什么? 我这个耳朵有点聋
I said, thank you. Thank you. You don't have to be annoying about it.
我说谢谢 谢谢你 你不要这么烦人
Do you wanna go grab a bite? I know a pizza place around the corner.
你想不想吃点东西? 我知道这拐弯角有家披萨店
You owe me an explanation for whatever that was.
你还没告诉我刚刚所有事的来龙去脉
- Yeah?  - Okay. You're right, I do.
- 怎么样?  - 好吧 你说的对 去吃吧
- Sure. Let's go.
- 好的 走吧
- Okay.  - Okay.
- 好的  - 好的
So I packed up my entire life and I followed him out here.
所以我离开家 跟着他来到这
And then six months later, I found him in bed with a Pilates instructor.
十六个月后 我发现他和一个普拉提教练上床
He's just not the guy I thought he was.
他并非我理想中的那个人
- I made a mistake.  - I don't believe in mistakes.
- 我犯了个错误  - 我的字典里没有错误
Well, that's a very convenient philosophy for someone like yourself.
是 对于你这样的人来说 这倒不失为一条很合适的人生观
It's the mistakes that make us who we are.
正是这些错误成就了现在的我们
They led you here, right?
它们引导你来这 对吗?
Would you rather be back in Atlanta right now?
你现在宁愿回亚特兰大吗?
No, not really.
不 不愿意
They led to your job, you like your job?
它们引导你找到了属于你的工作 你喜欢的你工作吗?
- I love my job.  - So there you go.
- 我爱我的工作  - 所以正是如此
Just saying.
一孔之见
- You're very smart.  - Mm-hm.
- 你很聪明  - 嗯
- Pretty smart for a club rat.  - Ha. Ouch.
- 就一个夜店烂人而言  - 哈 哦
- Good morning.  - Good morning, sir.
- 早上好  - 早上好 先生
Nice-looking woman from last night.
昨晚那个女人很漂亮
- You reconned my date.  - What? No. No.
- 你侦察了我的约会对象  - 什么? 没有 没有
Yeah, you did.
不 你做了
Okay. I'm sorry, I did. I reconned your date.
好吧 我很抱歉 我做了 我侦察了
- We had a deal.  - I know.
- 我们说好的  - 我知道
- Sorry, I started thinking...  - You started thinking?
- 对不起 我总胡思乱想...  - 你胡思乱想?
I had to find out... I didn't know.
我必须弄清楚... 我不知道
If there was some action, what were you gonna do?
如果当时可以采取行动 你会做什么?
- Call in Special Ops?  - No.
- 召集特别行动组?  - 不
- Sniper squad? Take me out?  - No, no. I mean...
- 狙击小队? 把我做掉?  - 不 不 我的意思是...
Our Munich office got a hit back on one of Heinrich's men from Hong Kong.
我们在慕尼黑的同事 遭到一个海因里希手下的反击 这人来自香港
Name is Ivan Sokolov.
名叫伊凡・索科洛夫
Here's a surveillance file from the DFS in Mexico.
这里有一份从墨西哥传来的数字频率合成技术的监控文件
We expect he's trying to get Heinrich into the country through L.A. Harbor.
我们预测 他将会试图让海恩里希从洛杉矶港口偷渡
Chatter suggests Ivan lives here in L.A.
数据表明他住在洛杉矶
Now, flush him out.
现在 把他清出来
She's definitely lost her sparkle.
她真不吸引人
All right, look, you flag Interpol, I'll call some of our contacts.
好的 这样 你发情报给国际刑警 我去联系线人
I really like this girl.
我真的很喜欢这个女孩
I really like her too.
我也很喜欢她
No, I really, really like her.
不 我真的真的很喜欢她
- So do I.  - You do?
- 我也是  - 你也是?
Yeah, I do.
是的 我也非常喜欢
- So you're not backing off?  - Nope.
- 所以你不会放弃?  - 不会
Okay.
好的
Then you ought to know that when we went out on our date, Lauren and I...
不过你应该了解 我们约会时 劳伦和我...
we, um....
我们 呃...
What?
怎么了?
What? What did you do?
怎么了? 你们做了什么?
We shared a kiss.
我们接吻了
- Wow.  - Mm-hm.
- 喔  - 嗯-哼
Incredibly magical kiss with tongue.
难以言喻的舌吻
Oh, dear. Wonderful.
哦 亲爱的 太美妙了
You are an animal.
你真是个色鬼
Look, pal, we kissed too.
听着 伙计 我跟她也接吻了
It was pretty special. I don't think it will be the last.
真的很与众不同 我不认为这是最后一次接吻
- Well, we'll see about that, won't we?  - We shall see about that.
- 好 我们等着看 对吧?  - 我们等着看吧
Yes, we will. We will see about that.
是的 我们会的 我们等着看
Don't do that. Don't say what I just said.
有意思吗? 不要老学我说话
We will see about that.
我们等着瞧
About that, we will see.
等着瞧 我们
We will see about that.
我们等着瞧
About that, we will see.
等着瞧 我们
Right. This is a live operation, it's a full wrap and tap, boys.
对 这次是全程监控行动 非常艰苦的任务 弟兄们
I want parabolics, infrareds, sat cams, everything we got on the job.
我需要麦克风 红外 照相机 卫星 我们工作中用的上的所有东西
I want you to acquire intel on one Lauren Scott.
我要你们去收集有关劳伦・斯科特的情报
- What are her secret likes....  - Dislikes.
- 她的私密喜好是什么...  - 不喜欢的
I want to know what makes her laugh, cry.
我想知道什么能让她笑 让她哭
Best friends, family members.
最好的朋友 家庭成员
Everything is important.
所有事情都很重要
The last three guys she slept with.
和她睡过的最后三个男人
Who she was sleeping with last week.
她上星期和谁睡过
You want us to take them out?
你想要我们干掉他们吗?
Yea...
是的...
No.
不
- No.  - I'm sorry, but...
- 不  - 对不起 但是...
- Does this have to do with Heinrich?  - That's level 5 classified.
- 这和海因里希有关系吗?  - 这是绝密信息
For my eyes only.
只能让我知道
This operation is top secret.
这次行动是绝对机密
- Don't let your country down, boys.  - Roger that.
- 别辜负了国家的期望 小伙子们  - 收到
# This is how we do it #
这就是我们的做法
# It's Friday night #
星期五的晚上
# And I feel all right #
我感觉不错
# And the party's here on the west side #
曼哈顿西区有个聚会
# So I reach for my 40 And I turn it up #
我够到播放器并调大
# Designated driver take the keys to my truck #
私家司机 拿着我车钥匙
# Hit the shore 'cause I'm faded. Honeys in the street say #
我们来到海滨 我醉了 街上的蜜蜂说
# Monty, yo, we made it #
蒙蒂 嗨 我们成功了
# It feels so good #
感觉真好
# In my 'hood tonight #
今晚我带着风帽
# The summertime skirts And the guys in Kani #
她们夏日短裙 他们穿着风衣
# All the gangbangers forgot about the drive-by #
少年飞车党也不出动了
# You gotta get your groove on #
得到报酬前
# Before you go get paid #
你必须好好专注
# So tip up your cup And throw your hands up #
那么微微倾斜你的酒杯 挥舞你的双手
# And let me hear the party say #
让我听到聚会的声音
# I'm kind of buzzed and it's all because #
我微微陶醉 因为
# This is how we do it #
这就是我们的做法
# To all my neighbors, you got much flavor #
我的邻居们 你们闻到了香味
# This is how we do it. Let's flip the track #
这就是我们的做法 让我们开向小道
# Bring the old school... #
带我们回母校...
Aww.
噢
# This is how we do it #
这就是我们的做法
# All hands are in the air #
手在空气中摇摆
# Wave them from here to there #
左右挥挥手
# If you're an O.G. mack #
如果你是一位健硕的运动员
# Or a wanna-be player #
或是一位梦想指挥家
# You see, the hood's been good to me #
你看 这个风帽多适合我
# Ever since I was a lower-case G #
以前我只是个小人物
# But now I'm a big G #
但如今已是今非昔比
# Let me hear the party say #
让我听到聚会的声音
# If you were from #
如果你和我
# Where I'm from then you would know #
来自同一地方 那你就应该知道
# This is how we do it #
这就是我们的做法
- What the hell is going on in here?  - Nothing.
- 这是在干什么?  - 没什么
Sorry to interrupt playtime, but we have an address on Ivan Sokolov.
很抱歉打扰你们娱乐 但是我们得到了伊凡・索科洛夫的住址
But I thought you boys might wanna get out of the office.
我刚还以为你们两个可能想离开办公室透透气呢
Absolutely.
当然想
I'll take lead, you run backup.
我先上 你支援
No, I was thinking of taking lead on this one, thank you.
不行 我刚想这次我先上 谢谢
- I'm always the first in the door.  - You're not always first at everything.
- 我一直都是先踏进门的  - 不是所有事情你都是居先
Hello. We're, um, friends of Ivan.
你好 我们是 呃 伊凡的朋友
Oh, no, take lead, please.
哦 不 请你带头
No, no. Honestly, after you.
不 不 真心实意 你先
- Brut?  - Patchouli.
- 低糖香槟?  - 广藿香
I love patchouli. Lovely.
我喜欢广藿香 真好闻
- Oh, no, I'm like...  - Yeah. What are you betting down there?
- 哦 不 我喜欢...  - 是 你打算去那赌什么?
Hello! Cards!
你好! 纸牌!
Mate, I am such a huge fan of poker.
老兄 我可是扑克牌的大粉丝
He actually won the Go Fish Masters tournament in Reno.
他可是赌城雷诺钓鱼大师赛的获胜者
This is private game.
这是私人游戏
Don't wave your hands at me, chief. Don't you know who I am?
不要朝我摆手 头儿 你不知道我是谁吗?
He got into the ros at brunch, he's gonzo.
他喝醉了 早午餐时喝多了 他现在有些不清醒
I said this is private game.
我说了这是私人游戏
I know who you are, mate.
我们认识你 老兄
- Ivan.  - The terrible.
- 伊凡  - 一个坏蛋
We're friends with Karl Heinrich.
我们是卡尔・海因里希的朋友
There's one little problem.
这有点小问题
Heinrich doesn't have any friends.
海恩里希没有任何朋友
Oh, dear.
哦 哎呀
Mag! Give me a mag!
弹夹! 给我一个弹夹!
Do you ever come prepared?
你就不能自己备带一次吗?
Bollocks, mate. Bollocks!
胡说 老兄 胡说!
Get out your gun.
掏枪
Tuck, get down!
塔克 趴下!
Get down!
趴下!
- There you are. I got you, eh, mate?  - No, I got him.
- 好了 我抓到你了 嗯 老兄  - 不 是我抓的
Yeah, of course you did, mate. I love your work.
是 当然是你抓的 你干得不错
Tell us where Heinrich is and we'll be able to cut you a deal, Ivan.
告诉我们海恩里希在哪 我们会帮你减刑的 伊凡
I'm not saying anything.
我什么都不会说的
Okay, you get three square meals a day and we'll get you a nice pair of trousers.
好吧 你一天会有三顿饱餐 而且我们会给你一条漂亮的裤子
- Let's go.  - Give deodorant a chance, Ivan. You stink.
- 走吧  - 伊凡 喷点除臭剂 你太臭了
- What's happening?  - Hm?
- 发生什么事了?  - 啊?
- What's going on?  - Uh, Collins. I'm gonna go see the medic.
- 怎么了?  - 呃 是柯林斯 我打算去军医那看看
- Yeah.  - You?
- 好  - 你去吗?
No. Just the intel flash coming over.
不用 我去查看信息
- Roger that.  - Right. Right.
- 收到  - 好的 好
She texted her friend Trish.
她发短信给了她的朋友翠西
Said she needed to talk because she was F-T-F-O.
说她想聊聊 因为她已经F-T-F-O
Which Cryptography Department believes means she was freaking the fuck out, sir.
解密部门意思是说 她快TMD要奔溃了 长官
I S-H-I-T you not. I was L-M-F-A-O when I read that.
我没胡说 我当时读到时完全不明白
- It was crazy, ridiculous...  - Bothwick! S-H-H-H-H-H.
- 这有点疯狂 荒谬...  - 博斯威克! 闭嘴
Trish then called the babysitter and told her it was an emergency.
翠西接着打电话给临时保姆 还告诉她这是紧急事件
This is serious. This is really serious.
很严重 真的很严重
Can't believe this is my problem. Last month, I was dating Boggle.
难以置信我现在居然在为此而困扰 上个月 我还在和前任约会呢
This month, two gorgeous guys.
这个月 就有两个极品男人
I need you to stop making references to Boggle like a man. It's a game.
求你了 别说得前任像个男人一样 只是个游戏
And you sound like a woman who has nine cats and knits her ass off.
而且你听起来像是 养猫猫织毛衣的老姑婆
You never said gorgeous. You said good-looking. There's a difference...
你从没用极品评价过谁 你说他们很帅 但这是不同的...
- Wanna see a picture of them?  - Yes.
- 你想看看他们的照片吗?  - 当然
- Okay.  - I didn't know you had pictures. Give it.
- 好的  - 我都不知道你还有照片 给我看看
Oh. Wow.
哦 喔
- Right?  - That's dirty sex.
- 是吧?  - 真是太性感了
You know you're gonna have dirty sex and it's gonna stink.
你知道你如果和他做爱可不太好
Not like sex. I mean, like, man stink, the good stuff.
不是不喜欢性爱 我的意思是说 就好比 男人味 好货色
That's pretty impressive. For you, yeah. What does the other one look like?
真羡慕你 真的 另一个家伙长什么样
You just scroll over, you do the finger thing.
你只要翻滚过去 点击一下
Oh, my God. He is hot too.
哦 天呐 他也很惹火
I am impressed with you.
真佩服你
- This is hotness. That man is...  - You scared the shit out of me.
- 这个很惹火 这个男人是...  - 你吓死我了
- You all right?  - Yup.
- 你还好吗?  - 很好
- Medically speaking?  - Fine.
- 从医学角度来说?  - 很好
- They're people, not products.  - You're not a very good liar, know that?
- 他们是人 不是商品  - 知道吗? 你不会说谎
- Oh, yes, and you are.  - They never play this game with me.
- 哦 是啊 彼此彼此  - 他们不是和我闹着玩的
Seeing as we're both here, we might as well share resources.
既然我们都在 那不妨分享资源
- Incredible guys.  - I guess I don't have a choice.
- 不可思议的家伙  - 你来都来了
- Please, sit down.  - Oh, I'm staying.
- 请吧 坐下  - 哦 我会待在这的
Okay, good, good. Well, I'm available as a friend.
好的 很好 很好 喂 我可是很够意思的
If you want me to have sex with both of those guys...
如果你想要我和他们两个做爱...
just to test out stuff and see who comes back a winner and who doesn't.
彻底考验他们 看看他俩谁能坚持到最后
They wouldn't know. I'd pretend I was you. I'd put my hair up in a pony.
他们不会知道的 我装成是你 我把头发盘起来
Obviously I'm busy, because I'm a mother, but I would carve out time in my schedule.
显然我是很忙 因为我还要照看孩子 但是我可以时间安排许可的情况下挤出一些空闲
That's the kind of friend I am.
我就是这样的朋友
- Why is she listening to that old man?  - I have no idea.
- 她为什么要听那个老家伙的?  - 我怎么知道
- Okay. You know what? That's not helpful.  - Okay, fine.
- 好吧 我觉得 那没什么用  - 好吧 无所谓
Then why don't we do one of your "focus groups" you do at work.
我们为什么不试试你讲课用的那种"小组讨论"方法
You can be the focus group, I can be in charge, like you.
你是小组里的人 我是像你一样的主管
- Oh, that's actually a good idea.  - Okay.
- 哦 这个主意不错  - 好吧
This is good, I like this.
那就这么办了 我也觉得不错
Okay, so I will ask you questions about the products.
好了 现在我要问你关于产品的事情
- Okay.  - The people.
- 好的  - 我是说男人
And you tell me who you like and why.
你告诉我 你喜欢谁 还有原因
I don't know. They're both incredible.
我也不知道 他们都很棒
What a struggle. I have to go home...
这么纠结的话 我就要回家了...
and clean tartar sauce out of Bob's beard right now.
我还得赶回去清理 鲍勃胡子上的蛋黄酱呢
Probably one of his testicles.
没准儿他蛋蛋上也沾到了
You're gonna sit here and talk to me about how amazing these guys are.
你只想干坐着跟我说这两个男人有多棒
- Is there anything bad about them?  - Okay, let me think. Flaws.
- 他们就没有缺陷吗?  - 让我想想 缺陷
I think there...
我觉得...
there is one thing.
倒是有一点
FDR has these tiny, like, girl hands. Like little T. rex hands.
富兰克林的手很小 像女孩子的一样 有点霸王龙的感觉
- Ha!  - Oh, gross.
- 哈!  - 哦 真恶心
Means he's got a Mike and lke for a penis.
那他的鸡巴估计也不大
You know that's not true. You've seen it.
这明显是瞎说 你看过的
You've seen it in Bangladesh, you know that's not true.
在孟加拉的时候 你看到过的 你知道这不是真的
And Tuck is British.
而塔克 就是个英国人
Mm.
这样啊
- What is that supposed to mean?  - Doesn't mean anything.
- 这是什么意思?  - 这样说明不了什么
That's the same, they're kind of even. So get into decision-making mode.
看来两个人不相上下 现在进入决策模式
And I need you to do it kind of quickly. It's fun, but I'm not the one having sex.
要赶快和他们做爱 反正挺好玩的 但不是我和他们做爱
- So I can't be that invested.  - Okay. You know what I need?
- 所以我不能评判太多  - 好吧 你知道我需要什么吗?
Mm.
知道
- A joint.  - No, I need a deadline.
- 3P  - 不 我要定个截止日期
- Okay.  - So I may gonna give myself a finite amount of time to make this decision.
- 好吧  - 我要让自己在一定期限内作出决定
- That's good.  - One week I have to make a decision.
- 很好啊  - 我要在一周内作出决定
One week?
一周?
Okay, so she grew up in Georgia.
她出生在乔治亚州
She likes to volunteer at dog shelters.
喜欢去动物保护所做义工
She's a fan of classic rock and collecting mini Camaros.
她喜欢古典摇滚 喜欢收集迷你大黄蜂
What, as in the cars?
什么 喜欢车?
This is so fun!
太刺激了!
You're a natural in this.
你开车太有天赋了
It's just so weird. My dad used to collect these.
太神奇了 我爸爸以前喜欢收集这种车
They were never as nice as this one. But he never let me drive them.
它们都没这辆好 不过他从来不让我开
I can't possibly imagine why he wouldn't do that.
想不出他为什么不让你开
# She's got a magic spell on me #
我对她的魔力着了迷
Did he just give our bird the bird?
他刚刚对我们的摄像头竖中指了?
# Now I've got a woman #
我已经有了心爱的女人
- What was that?  - What? Well, that was the exhaust.
- 那是什么?  - 什么? 在排尾气吧
- Oh.  - Give it some throttle. Go on.
- 哦  - 快加大马力 冲啊
She likes red wine, lavender bath salts.
她喜欢红酒 薰衣草浴盐
And she collects posters by Gustav Klimt.
还有收集克林姆的海报
- Huh?  - Yeah. Austrian cat. Boy can paint.
- 什么?  - 对啊 就是那个奥地利人 从小会画画
Ain't you never seen "the Kiss"? You know, like that...
难道你没看过那幅油画"吻"吗? 就像这样...
Yeah, no, of course I have.
当然 我当然看过
Is this what I think it is?
我看到的不是真的吧?
You're a fan?
你是他的粉丝?
- of Gustav Klimt?  - Of Gustav Klimt.
- 克林姆的粉丝?  - 克林姆的粉丝
- He's my favorite artist.  - He's my favorite artist.
- 他是我最喜欢的艺术家  - 他是我最喜欢的艺术家
This is incredible.
太不可思议了
- Are these real?  - Yeah.
- 这些都是真品吗?  - 没错
Okay, stop.
哦 不会吧
- You recognize this?  - Yes.
- 认出这幅了吗?  - 当然
- "The Harpist", 1895?  - I have this...
- 1895年的"竖琴师"?  - 我有这个...
- Seen it in a book.  - Pre-secession movement.
- 在书里看到过  - 维也纳分离危机
Look at the tension between two and three dimensionality.
注意看第二根弦 和第三根之间分开的距离
Do you see the tension between two and three dimensionality?
你看到第二根弦 和第三根之间分开的距离了吗?
- Incredible.  - How do you know?  - This is my favorite.
- 真是难以置信  - 你怎么知道?  - 这幅是我的最爱
"Undine", 1902.
1902年的"金鱼"
Oh, my goodness, this is amazing.
哦 我的天呐 太不可思议了
Innovation became intrinsic....
对于德加和其他现代主义者来说...
to Degas and other modernists. You can see influence of art nouveau.
革新是必然的 可以看出他受了新的艺术形式的影响
He was a strong advocate of finger-painting movement.
他是手指画运动的强烈倡导者之一
What?
什么?
Hey. We lost contact.
嘿 我们没信号了
Sometimes he would finger his paintings to get closer to them.
有时候 他会用手指来作画以接近他们
He, uh, used his....
他 呃 用他的...
He would...
他会...
The intimacy with the canvas to finger a painting...
用手指去作画 以增强油画的亲近感...
to...
去...
Rather to paint using hands.
而不是用手作画
Sometimes, he would use mud and sticks.
有时候 他也会用泥土和棍子
You know, he used mud and sticks... Ahem.
他也用泥土和棍子... 嗯嗯
He did?
他用过吗?
- If he couldn't find a stick...  - If he couldn't find a stick...
- 如果他找不到棍子...  - 如果他找不到棍子...
- he would use his dick.  - he'd just use his...
- 他就用自己的鸡巴  - 他就用自己的...
What?
什么?
Oh, son of a bitch. Who is...?
哦 混蛋 是谁...?
- Ha, ha.  - Ugh!
- 哈哈  - 啊!
You know, I think enough talking.
好了 我觉得我不用再说下去了
Let's let the paintings speak for themselves.
好的画作 是会自己说话的
Oh, my God.
哦 上帝啊
Wow.
哇喔
That is so beautiful.
太美了
It's amazing.
真不可思议
Just incredible.
太难以置信了
Yeah. It is.
是啊 没错
Thank you.
谢谢
- Hello?  - Hey, it's me.
- 喂?  - 嘿 是我
- How did it go?  - They both went well. Too well.
- 进展如何?  - 他们都表现得太好了 非常好
- I don't know what to do.  - That's awesome. I'm coming over.
- 我不知道要怎么办了  - 很不错嘛 我过来再说
Go up on 5. Let's just pump the audio a little bit.
调到5频道 把声音调大一点
Are you sure about this, sir? We might have some constitutional issues here.
确定能转吗 长官? 我们可能会触犯宪法噢
Patriot Act.
根据爱国者法案
- So how was it?  - They're both incredible.
- 怎么样了?  - 他俩都太不可思议了
Uh, FDR has these amazing eyes that you just wanna melt into.
呃 富兰克林的眼神能让你想要融化进去
So beautiful. He brings out the best in me.
太美了 他能激发我最好的状态
He really challenges me.
对我来说 真的很有挑战
But he's that guy who's always on, he's superslick.
但是我觉得他 比较自我 很圆滑
Sometimes, I think he doesn't care about anything more than himself.
有时候 我会觉得他除了自己以外 谁都不在乎
Well, they say it's a sanctuary for them, but it's... Here it is.
据说这里是它们的保护所 但是... 就这里了
- This is amazing.  - It's really more of a sanctuary for me.
- 这里太棒了  - 这里对我来说 不只是保护所
- Hey, Rebecca.  - Who's that man?
- 嘿 丽贝卡  - 那人是谁?
- Hey, Betty.  - Excuse me?
- 嘿 贝蒂  - 什么?
I just had no idea you were so passionate about animals.
没想到你这么喜欢小动物
Yeah. Animals and kids.
是啊 不只小动物 还有小朋友
What's up?
你好啊?
- How you doing, Nick?  - What?
- 最近怎么样 尼克?  - 什么?
There are a lot of things you don't know about me...
你不知道的事情还有很多...
- and it takes a while for me to open up.  - I can see that.
- 我需要时间 慢慢展示给你  - 我能看出来的
Oh, what's the matter?
哦 怎么啦?
- What's the matter, you?  - Hey, little guy.
- 你怎么啦?  - 嘿 小家伙
- What's going on?  - You okay?
- 怎么回事?  - 你还好吗?
- Are you allowed to open the cages?  - All the time.
- 他们允许你打开笼子吗?  - 随时可以
- Okay.  - Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 好吧  - 哦 没事 没事 没事
- Hey, Snuggles, how are you, bud?  - It's a Boston terrier.
- 嘿 依依 你怎么啦?  - 这只是波士顿梗犬
I love these dogs. Hi.
我超爱这种狗 你好啊
Hi.
你好啊
Yeah. That's a lot of energy.
它真有活力啊
I love this place.
我太喜欢这里了
Mm.
嗯
- What's in your mouth?  - A lot of dog hair.
- 你嘴里怎么了?  - 都是狗毛
- Yeah.  - So....
- 是啊  - 所以...
I know.
都是毛
Big mess.
乱七八糟的
- Do you wanna help me pick one out?  - You're gonna adopt a dog?
- 你想帮我挑一只吗?  - 你想收养只狗?
I think it's time for me to be responsible for something other than myself, you know?
我觉得是时候承担起一些责任了 而不是只顾自己 你明白吗?
Wow, I think that's so great.
喔 你的想法太棒了
Okay.
好的
Let's pick the saddest, oldest bastard here.
我们挑只最惨 最老的狗吧
Okay, what about Tuck?
塔克怎么样?
Uh, Tuck is great.
呃 塔克很好
He's sweet, he's kind... We have so much fun.
他很贴心 很善良... 我们在一起很开心
More fun that I've ever had in my entire life.
是我这辈子过得最开心的日子了
But he's maybe too sweet? A little earnest?
但是和他也许太甜蜜了? 太过温柔?
Uh, sort of safe.
呃 没有安全感
Yeah. That's boring. I almost fell asleep just listening to that.
也是 那样很无聊的 听你说这些我都快睡着了
Safe.
安全感
Hey Tuck, I think I'm ready.
嘿塔克 我准备好了
- You ever carried a weapon before?  - You know...
- 你以前拿过枪吗?  - 这个...
Not really, no.
其实没有过
Okay. Okay. I need you to keep that end of the weapon well away from me, clear?
没事 没事 你可别把枪头对着我噢 明白吗?
- Okay.  - Thumbs up.
- 明白  - 很好
- This will be fun.  - No.
- 会很好玩的  - 不
It's not fun.
不是好玩
It's dangerous.
会很危险
Hey, watch there.
嘿 看好了
- Men! Move.  - My face!
- 伙计们! 让一让  - 我的脸!
Oh, my God.
哦 天呐
Man, come on.
老兄 你不是吧
- Come on.  - Oh!
- 跟上  - 哦!
Okay.
来了
Oh, God, I gotta get the goggles on. This is very stressful!
哦 天呐 我要戴好护目镜 这太刺激了
- Clear. We're coming out. Okay, come on.  - Okay.
- 没有敌人 我们可以出来了 跟上  - 好的
Get him!
找到他了!
- No head shots!  - That's illegal.
- 不能爆头!  - 你违规的
Oh, my God.
哦 天呐
I'm scared.
我害怕
It's a grenade!
是手榴弹!
# How you like me now #
现在你爱死我了吧
Who is that guy?
那人是谁?
It's just a game. Ah!
不就是个游戏嘛!
Let's get out of here.
我们快撤吧
Huh? Oh, yes.
怎样? 哦 好的
Oh, my God.
哦 天呐
- Did you see me light that up?  - Okay.
- 看到我夺到旗子了吧?  - 是啊
That boy come right out of nowhere.
那小子不知道从哪冒出来的
Okay, you are disturbingly good at this.
你竟然擅长玩这个 太让我震惊了
Oh, yeah. Yeah, how does that make you feel?
哦 是啊 是啊 你感觉怎样?
Like if our nation gets attacked by random paintball people...
我觉得 如果我们国家被彩弹人攻击了...
- I'll be safe.  - Safe.
- 我会很安全  - 安全
I tried to get your back there. I got off a few shots...
我试着掩护你 自己还中了几枪...
but I think my triggering mechanism was stuck.
不过我的扳机好像卡住了
- You got the safety on.  - I was trying to...
- 你保险开着的吧  - 我本来想...
- Oh, you mean this thing here?  - Yeah. Ugh!
- 哦 你是说这个开关?  - 是的 呃!
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
哦 天呐 你还好吧?
Ha, ha. Oh, I'm sorry I'm laugh...
哈 哈 哦 不好意思我笑了...
I have this laughter thing when bad things happen.
我总是幸灾乐祸
It's not funny. I shouldn't do that.
这不好笑 我不应该笑
Are you okay? Can you walk?
你没事吧? 能走路吗?
Yeah, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
可以 没事 没事 没事
Oh, my God, I feel so bad.
哦 上帝啊 太抱歉了
Yeah, it's good.
没事 我没事
- Come on, let's go get something to eat.  - Okay.
- 走吧 我们去吃点东西  - 好的
So you know how I was telling you that Tuck has been really earnest?
还记得我那天跟你说 塔克太温柔吗?
The other day, we went paintballing...
第二天我们就去玩彩弹野战了...
and he nearly put this kid's eye out with a paintball gun.
他差点把人家眼珠打爆了
Then FDR, we went to this animal shelter...
还有富兰克林 我们去了动物保护所...
and he adopted a 12-year-old dog with a milky eye.
他领养了一只很老的狗狗 有一只眼睛是白内障
I'm telling you, it's getting weird.
我觉得 真的很奇怪
I can't help but thinking I'm putting them in this position.
我不禁在想 我让他们处于这种境地
It's making them crazy. It's making me crazy.
会把他们弄疯的 也会把我自己弄疯的
So, what are you gonna do about it?
那你打算怎么办呢?
I have to do what any rational woman in my position would do.
在这种处境下 我要做任何理性的女人 都会做的事
- Break up with them?  - Sleep with them.
- 和他们分手?  - 和他们上床
Sex tiebreaker.
做爱决胜负
Oh, thank you! Finally!
哦 谢天谢地! 终于!
A sex tiebreaker! That is what you need to do!
做爱决胜负! 就是要这样!
You have to have sex with both of them!
你要和他们两个人做爱!
Thank you.
谢天谢地
What? It's called the birds and the bees, bitch, okay? Google it.
怎么了? 这只是初级性教育好不好? 不信去网上搜
We had a deal.
我们有言在先的
Well, we have a deal.
对 我们有言在先
- We have a deal.  - I'm not gonna have sex with her.
- 有言在先的  - 我不会和她做爱
And I am not gonna have sex with this woman either.
我也不会和她做爱
No matter how hard she tries.
不管她用什么方法
- We have a gentleman's agreement.  - We have a gentleman's agreement.
- 我们有君子协定的  - 我们有君子协定
And we are gentlemen.
我们都是君子
Okay?
对吧?
Ha-ha-ha. Okay.
哈哈哈 对的
- Okay.  - Good.
- 好的  - 很好
Good Lord.
好家伙
- That the time?  - Yeah, I got that thing.
- 几点了?  - 哦 我还有事情
I gotta be somewhere this time.
我也有地方要去
Full-scale tactical prevention mode.
全面战备模式
What exactly do you have in mind?
你在计划些什么?
Yeah.
耶
Wow, this is amazing.
哇喔 太美了
- Indeed.  - How nice.
- 确实  - 真浪漫
- Do you think the candles are a bit cheesy?  - No. I think they're wonderful.
- 蜡烛是不是有点太老套了?  - 不会 我觉得很棒
This has been the perfect night.
今晚太完美了
Dickerman...
迪克曼 准备好...
make it rain.
下雨
# Can't stand it #
忍不了了
# I know you planned it I'm gonna set it straight #
我知道是你干的 我要让你暴露在众目睽睽之下
# Sabotage #
破坏行动
You really think you can trust him?
你觉得他可信吗?
Absolutely not.
当然不可信
- Okay, I believe you.  - Wow.
- 到了 相信你会喜欢  - 哇喔
- This is great.  - Yeah?
- 太棒了  - 是吗?
Yeah.
是啊
- Pool on the roof.  - Oh, you know...
- 还有屋顶游泳池  - 哦 这个是...
it's hydrotherapy for an old football injury.
为以前踢球的旧伤 做做水疗什么的
I'll be right back.
等我去下洗手间
- Okay?  - Okay.
- 好吗?  - 好的
Come on, scram. Let's go.
快点 闪开 一边去
# He moves in space #
他来回徘徊
Ah! God.
啊 见鬼
# It's a sabotage #
开始破坏行动
# Can't stand it I know you planned it #
忍不了了 我知道是你干的
Son of a...
你这个混...
# I can't stand rocking When I fly off the handle #
当我飞奔而出 我忍不住开始摇滚
# What could it be? It's a mirage #
怎么会这样? 是幻觉
# You're scheming on a thing, hat's sabotage #
你想搞阴谋破坏
# Smooth operator #
圆滑的男人
FDR?
你睡着了 富兰克林?
# Smooth operator #
圆滑的男人
Really?
不是吧?
# Smooth operator #
圆滑的男人
A tranq dart.
麻醉枪
A tranq dart. Three inches over, I would've been dead.
竟然用麻醉枪 偏三英寸的话 我就挂了
Four. Four inches, okay?
四 四英寸 好吧?
- Neanderthal.  - Morning, sirs.
- 原始人  - 早上好 先生们
Shut up.
闭嘴
Jesus. I cannot believe you didn't trust me.
天啊 真不敢相信 你竟然不相信我
We both know what happens when you listen to Sade.
听萨德的话 大家都知道结果如何
- She's an incredible singer.  - She is.
- 她是一位很赞的歌手  - 没错
Your hormones start, you turn into Horny Pants.
你的荷尔蒙开始分泌 之后你就开始荡漾了
- Hor...  - And might I remind you...
- 荡...  - 还有 别忘了...
you were the one who flooded my apartment first.
是你先冲进我家打乱我计划的
- The candles were a fire hazard.  - No.
- 蜡烛本来就是火灾隐患  - 才怪
The only thing you were worried about getting fired up was Lauren, wasn't it?
你唯一担心的 就是怕劳伦欲火焚身 对不对?
Honesty, Franklin.
说实话 富兰克林
Try it.
走着瞧
Right!
好了!
Now, I have very serious anger management issues today, Ivan...
我今天非常不爽 伊凡...
so I would appreciate it if you'd do me the courtesy...
我不会为难你的 只要你能...
of answering all my terribly boring questions...
配合回答我所有无聊的问题...
sharpish.
不许拐弯抹角
- Heh, heh. The pliers, really?   - Yes, the pliers, really.
- 呵呵 老虎钳 开玩笑吧?  - 不是 是老虎钳 没错
- Predictable, safe and boring yet again.  - Why don't you tickle Ivan's feet...
- 早就猜到了 你还是那么保守和无聊  - 不如你去挠伊凡的痒痒...
till he talks with your teeny, tiny, itty-bitty jazz hands?
一直挠到他告诉你 你那比划着爵士手势的手是有多么的小巧玲珑?
Heh.
呵
Where is Heinrich, brother?
伙计 海因里希到底在哪?
Sooner or later he'll be coming for you.
早晚他会找你算账的
Brother.
兄弟
You are going to die.
你活不了多久的
Don't worry, you're next.
别担心 下一个就是你
中央情报局外勤办公室
洛   杉   矶   港
I'm sorry about Jonas.
对乔纳斯 我感到很遗憾
- Tuck, I gotta talk to you about Nana's.  - Sure. Whose car are we taking tonight?
- 塔克 我想和你谈谈关于去奶奶那的事  - 好啊 今晚开谁的车去呢?
I don't think it's gonna work out tonight. You don't want me there?
- 今晚怕是不行了  - 你不想让我去
It's not that. It's...
不是这样的 只是...
I invited Lauren.
我邀请了劳伦
Oh, wow. Uh...
噢 不错噢
It's a nice move, isn't it? Meet the family. What are you, Garry Kasparov?
这步棋下的妙啊 对吧? 见家长了 难道你就是传说中的格里・卡斯帕罗夫吗？
It's not like that. Lauren's been asking about them, and you know Nana.
不是这么回事 劳伦一直在询问家里人的事 你也了解奶奶的
Once she heard I was dating someone, she got excited. She wanted to meet them.
她一听说我谈朋友了 她就兴奋不已 想见见她们呢
- I don't believe this.  - What?
- 真不敢相信这一切  - 怎么了?
This is not a play to one-up you. They're my family.
我并没有要先你一步的意思 他们可是我的家人啊
- Yeah, but they're my family too.  - Yeah, but they're my actual family.
- 对啊 但是他们也是我的家人啊  - 没错 但是他们和我可是有血缘关系的呀
- Wow. Yeah.  - Ahem.
- 喔 说的好  - 呃哼
Of course they are.
确实是这样的
How silly of me.
我真蠢啊
Ooh! Oh, gosh. No, no, no. Just let him do his thing.
哦! 哦 天啊 不 不 不 别管他
Oh, hello.
哦 你好
Uh, Nana, this is Lauren. Lauren, this is my grandmother, Nana.
呃 娜娜 这是劳伦 劳伦 这是我祖母 娜娜
So you're the girl who's been putting up with Franklin.
这么说来 富兰克林一直欺负的就是你了
- Mm-hm.  - I brought pie.
- 嗯嗯  - 我带了馅饼
Yeah, you know where the kitchen is. Lauren and I have a lot to talk about.
好的 放到厨房里去吧 我和劳伦要好好谈谈
Yes, this is pretty, isn't it?
是啊 这里真美啊 对不对?
Oh, this is beautiful.
哦 真是太漂亮了
- Oh, is this FDR?  - Oh, yes.
- 哦 这是富兰克林?  - 哦 是的
Look at that unibrow.
看看他的连心眉
- It goes all the way around his head.  - I know, he was so cute.
- 一直长到头上  - 我知道 他很帅
- Hi, Dottie.  - And who are these people?
- 嗨 多蒂  - 这些人是谁?
Oh, those are his parents.
哦 那是他父母
They died when he was 9.
他们在他9岁时去世了
I'm so sorry.
抱歉
- He never told me that.  - Yeah.
- 他从未跟我提起过  - 是啊
In a car crash. They were going out to dinner one night and, um...
死于车祸 那天晚上 他们一起出去吃晚饭呢 呃...
Well, he's never been quite the same since.
从那时起 他就完全变了一个人
He has a hard time trusting people.
他不愿意去相信别人
But he must trust you.
但他肯定相信你
Because you are the first girl he's ever brought here.
因为他从不带女孩来这里 你是第一个
I have a hard time trusting people too.
我也不愿意相信别人
He had the biggest blue eyes, like marbles.
他的蓝色眼睛非常大 跟蓝色宝石一样
Which almost made up for the bed-wetting.
所以即便尿床 你也不会生他的气
Nana. We really don't have to talk about that right now.
娜娜 我们现在能不能不讲这些
- Oh, we really do.  - No, no, no.
- 哦 我们当然要谈  - 不 不 别啊
- No, we should.  - No, no, no.
- 不 我们要谈  - 不行 别说了啊
- We ought to.  - I know...
- 我们要谈  - 我知道...
He wore that Superman costume everywhere.
他去哪里都穿着那套超人服
You wouldn't believe the smell.
你肯定不会相信的
But how were we to know that he would take it so literally?
我们压根都没想到 他怎么能把随便的一句话就当真呢?
- The little fellow jumped off the roof.  - Oh!
- 那小家伙真的从屋顶上跳了下来  - 哦!
I was given misinformation, okay?
还不因为你们骗我 好吧?
We all make mistakes. That was one of mine.
我们都犯过错 那是其中一件
Yes, but remember, Franklin, there are no mistakes.
没错 但是你要记住 富兰克林 不存在对与错
To no mistakes.
敬不存在对与错
- To no mistakes.  - To no mistakes.
- 不存在对与错  - 不存在对与错
- Okay, wearing dresses.  - I was only wearing them...
- 好吧 穿连衣裙  - 我穿连衣裙...
because I thought they were capes.
是因为我把它们当披风了
Are we recording this?
要录下来吗?
I had a nice time tonight.
我今晚过得很愉快
Me too.
我也是
I like that guy with the unibrow and the braces.
我喜欢那个有连心眉 穿吊带的男人
- Ha, ha.  - I actually...
- 哈哈  - 其实我...
I might like him more than I like you.
比起你 我可能更喜欢他
He likes you too.
他也喜欢你
Ha, ha. I should go.
哈哈 我该走了
Yeah.
好的
I should be a gentleman.
我应该绅士一点
Well, the good news is I'm no gentleman.
呃 好消息是 我不是淑女
This is not good.
大事不好
# She blew my mind #
她让我无法自拔
# And we've been hangin' out #
我们也一直在约会
# Ever since that time #
从那次之后
# We got good love #
我们找到了真爱
# Rock 'n' roll #
一起摇滚吧
Oh, no.
哦 不
# Oh, yeah #
哦 就这样
# Sweet, sweet love #
甜蜜蜜的爱
- Hey.  - Oh, God!
- 嘿  - 哦 天啊!
Oh, my God. Okay.
哦 天啊 好吧
- Morning.  - Good morning.
- 早上好  - 早上好
- You're dressed. Where you going?  - I have to go to work.
- 你穿的这么整齐 要去哪里啊?  - 我要去上班
I thought maybe we could make pancakes or something.
我还以为我们能一块做煎饼呢
Do you like pancakes?
你喜欢煎饼吗?
I love pancakes. Really, I'd love to have pancakes.
我喜欢 真的 我想吃煎饼
- Who doesn't like pancakes? Crazy people.  - Crazy people.
- 谁不喜欢煎饼呢? 疯子吧  - 疯子
I have to go to work. I have a meeting.
我要去上班了 有个会要开
Really super early. So I gotta go.
会很早就要开始 所以 我要走了
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, no, that's cool.
好 好 好 好吧 不 没事
I have... I've got a meeting too, so...
我也... 我也有个会要开 因此...
- Okay.  - Last night was...
- 好吧  - 昨晚...
- Uh.... was...   - Was incredible.
- 呃... 真的...  - 真的很棒
That was crazy.
太疯狂了
Yeah.
是啊
Uh, thank you for the...
谢谢你...
Thank you for that.
谢谢你所做的一切
So I'm gonna go.
我要走了
But lock up behind you... Or don't lo... I don't know.
记得锁门... 别... 我不知道
You're not gonna steal anything, are you? I don't know why I said that.
你又不会偷我东西 对吧? 我不知道为什么要那么说
Okay, bye.
好吧 再见
Bye.
再见
Trish, I slept with him.
翠西 我跟他上床了
- Which one?   - FDR.
- 哪个?  - 富兰克林
Oh, my God, that's awesome. How do you feel? Can you walk?
哦 天啊 太好了 什么感觉? 你还能走路吗?
Small hands, not an issue.
手很小 但不是问题
I told you it wasn't gonna be an issue.
我就跟你说了 不会有问题的
How was it?
感觉怎么样?
Amazing. Like five times amazing.
很棒 非常非常棒
But I'm supposed to go meet Tuck this afternoon.
但我下午还要跟塔克见面
But after last night, I can't see Tuck now.
但昨晚那事之后 我现在不能去见塔克了
No, no, they do it to us all the time, okay?
不 不 他们向来都那么对我们 好吧?
You think Gloria Steinem got arrested and sat in jail...
你觉得葛罗莉亚・斯坦能被抓了 蹲在监狱...
so you could act like a little bitch? I don't think so. Get out there, you get flexible.
这样你就能像个荡妇一样? 我觉得不行 去吧 灵活应对
- I'm going to hell.  - You're not. If you go there, I'm...
- 我真是太无耻了  - 才不是 如果你去了 我...
I'll be there to pick you up.
我去接你
Okay, save me a drink.
好的 记得给我带饮料
You got last night's surveillance tape?
你有昨晚的监控录像吗?
Oh, hey, uh....
哦 嘿 呃...
We didn't get anything.
我们没录
We got nothing.
没录像
The tape jammed, so.... ha, ha.
带子卡了 因此... 哈哈
Boylee, it's digital, you plank.
波利 那是数码的 你个笨蛋
- Right. So can I have the disk?  - Yup.
- 行了 能把光盘给我吗?  - 好的
Seriously, you don't wanna see it.
说真的 你还是别看的好
I'll be the judge of that, thank you very much.
看不看我自己说了算 谢谢你
Now, did you see this?
我问你 你们看了吗?
Only once.
只看了一次
Right. What happened?
是啊 出什么事了?
Agent Foster entered the premises.
福斯特探员到跟她回家了
- All right.  - Yep.
- 好吧  - 真的
- And?  - Ha, ha.
- 然后呢?  - 哈哈
- Boylee.  - Ahem.
- 波利  - 嗯
- Then he...  - Boylee, what happened next?
- 然后他...  - 波利 然后怎么了?
Then he entered the premises.
然后他们上床了
I got it, mate. Yeah, I totally understand. Thank you very much. Cheers, mate.
我知道了 伙计 好的 我完全明白了 谢谢你 干杯 兄弟
Open your eyes.
睁开眼睛
I'm flying.
我在飞
Jack.
杰克
Hey.
嘿
- Hi.  - Maya.
- 嗨  - 玛雅
So it's Tuesday. Mm-hm?
今天是周二吗?
My layover day?
我今天休息?
Yeah. Right. Um....
是的 没错 嗯...
It's just...
只是...
Look, I...
听着 我...
I can't really do this, um....
我真的不能这么做 嗯...
I met somebody.
我有其他人了
Sorry.
对不起
Okay.
没事
What's happening to me?
我这是怎么了?
You have absolutely no self-control.
你完全控制不了你自己
Tuck, look, I didn't plan on this happening, okay?
塔克 听我说 我也不想这样的 好吧?
She's the one that initiated it in the first place.
是她先勾引我的
Well, of course she initiated.
呃 当然是她
You roll out the big, happy family, it's like girl porn, isn't it?
你们还真够疯狂的啊 整个就像是女子色情录像 不是吗?
- You broke the rules, man.  - Forget the rules. Not a game anymore.
- 你坏了规矩 伙计  - 忘了什么规矩吧 这不再是个游戏了
- I care for Lauren.  - Great, you have affections.
- 我喜欢劳伦  - 好的 你还是有感情的
- It only took you 30 years.  - Tuck.
- 这才过了30年 你就意识到了  - 塔克
- What?  - I slept with her.
- 怎么了?  - 我跟她上床了
- Yeah, well, I'm well aware of that, aren't I?  - No, slept. Fell asleep.
- 哦 好吧 我知道 好吧?  - 不 上床 然后睡着了
That's never happened to me before.
我以前从来没有过这种感觉
Okay, so he wants to play family, so we'll play families. We can play families. Right?
好吧 既然他想玩家庭这招 咱也奉陪到底 咱也玩得起 对吧?
- All right. Uh, yeah.  - Good, let's play families.
- 好啊 没问题  - 很好 咱也用这招
- I don't know what that means.  - It means get me a family.
- 说实话我没明白  - 意思是给我找帮人扮家人
Right, so you got your aliases. Back stories.
好的 别名 背景故事 吸引人的轶事
Charming anecdotes.
都准备好了吗?
Yeah? Great. Grandma, if you could pull out a few tears when you're telling that story...
都好了? 太好了 奶奶 你在讲我如何从水井里救出那位盲童时
of how I rescued the blind children from the well, there's an extra 50 in it for you.
要是能挤出两行眼泪 那我就再多付你50元
Right. Ladies, mental gents, I shall see you at 1300 hours.
好的 女士们先生们 咱们中午1点见
I am so glad you could make it on short notice.
在这么仓促的通知下 你能来我很开心
Yeah, I'm happy to be here.
我也很开心能来呀
And they are going to absolutely love you, and you will love them.
他们肯定会爱死你 你也会爱上他们的
- I'm excited.  - So am I. God, you look gorgeous.
- 我好迫不及待噢  - 我也是 天 你真是太美了
They should be here. I'm going to give them a ring. You mind?
他们应该到了吧 我去给他们打个电话 不介意吧?
Oh, not at all. Okay.
噢 怎么会 去吧
Okay. You look gorgeous.
好的 你真是太美了
Here we go boys. Here we go.
开始了 好戏要上演了
- Hi.  - There she is.
- 嗨  - 她在这呢
- How are you?  - Good. You?
- 你好吗   - 不错呢 你呢?
Supposed to be here three minutes ago.
三分钟前就该到的吧
They are not there yet.I don't understand. They should be there by now.
他们还没有到 搞不明白了 他们现在应该到了啊
- Yeah, well, they're not, are they?  - Okay, let me find out what happened.
- 他们确实不在 好不好?  - 好的 我去查查
- Ha, ha. So, finally. Right?  - Yeah.
- 哈 哈 终于见到你了啊  - 是啊
Oh, bollocks.
噢 妈的
- So has he told you?  - What?
- 那么他和你说了吗?  - 说什么?
- How he got his name. "Tuck."  - No, he didn't.
- “塔克”这个名字的由来  - 没呢
Oh, not his given name. Not at all. "Tuck." Unusual, right?
噢 这并不是他的真名 绝对不是 "塔克" 很少见 对吧?
- Yeah. Yeah.  - Oh, here he is.
- 是啊 是啊  - 噢 他来了
Hi. Your Dad was just telling me how you got your nickname.
嗨 你老爸正在和我讲你外号的由来呢
Hello, son.
好啊 儿子
Hello, Dad.
好啊 老爸
- Hello.  - How are...? Unh... Unh... Unh...
- 好啊  - 你还...? 嗯... 噢...嗯...
- Oh, my good...  - Mm-mm.
- 噢 我的天...  嗯..嗯
- Jolly good.  - Right.
- 太好了  - 是啊
Right, we're just getting to it. Old Tuckers comes down one day.
好的 故事才刚开始呢 小塔克有一天
I don't know, he's 10 or 11, wearing a dress.
记不太清了 10岁还是11岁 穿着一条长裙
Hikes it up and goes, "Oh, look. I've got me naughty bits tucked under."
把裙子提起来说"噢 快瞧啊 我把我淘气的小鸡鸡藏进去了"
Hence, "Tuck."
因此得名 "塔克"
"I'd fuck me. I'd fuck me." "What's wrong with this boy?"
" 我都想干我自己 我都想干我自己" "这小孩到底是闹哪样啊?"
But it doesn't matter because, like, we're just so proud that Tuck is into girls again.
都无所谓了 塔克又对女孩感兴趣了 我们都很自豪呢
- Finally.  - Because for a while it was all Egyptian men.
- 果不其然  - 因为他有一阵可是很迷埃及男人的
Yeah. "Oh, gotta have it coming and going. Please." Whoo-woo!
对啊 " 噢 来来往往呀" 喔 喔!
Choo-choo train.
火车要开啦
"Come on, boys, have at it. It's the navy."
"拜托 孩子 睁大眼睛看啦 是船队啦"
Ahem. I think we should order.
啊哼 咱们还是点餐吧
Lauren, Tuck really is, like, a really great brother.
劳伦 塔克真的 真的是一位还哥哥
He is. He saved me from becoming a swinger.
他 要不是因为他 俺差点就成了荡妇
Before Tuck stepped in, everyone in our village used to call me "The Sausage Wallet."
塔克帮我前 村里的人们都叫俺"公厕"
- "TSW." That's a Shakespearean term for slut.  - Right.
- "TSW" 莎士比亚用来形容荡妇的词  - 没错
Where did you find her?
你从哪找到这货的啊?
So, what's going on with your bits up top ? Heard they weren't real. They look real to me.
你那对奶子是怎么回事? 听说不是真的啊 我看起来倒是挺真的
- Tuck said they were fake.  - What?
- 塔克和俺们说你的胸是假的  - 什么?
- I did not. I wouldn't say...  - "These knockers. Oh!
- 我才没有 我怎么可能会说...  - "这对奶子 噢!
- Can't wait to get into them."  - I wouldn't say that.
- 真想好好揉揉啊"  - 我绝对没这么说过
- You did. Why you lying now?  - Yeah, but they look quite nice.
- 就是你说的 怎么不敢承认了呢?  - 是啊 不过看起来确实很挺啊
- Not as big as these bazookas, but...  - Wait, is there a waiter?
- 和这对巨无霸比起来还有点差距 但..  - 慢着 服务员人呢?
You know what, actually, I forgot I have a commitment at work.
打断一下 我想起来了我还有点公事要忙
It's been very nice meeting you all, but I have to go.
见到你们真的很高兴 不过我得先走了
- You want something to go, then?  - No, thank you.
- 不打包点吃的吗?  - 不了 多谢
Wait, can I get your cell number?
等等 能给俺你的电话号码吗?
- God.  - Lauren.
- 上帝啊  - 劳伦
- Bring up six.  - Bringing.
- 切换到6号监控  - 好的
- Sorry about that.  - What was that? That was the weirdest five minutes of my life.
- 刚才很抱歉  - 搞什么啊?那是我人生最莫名其妙的5分钟
I'm sorry. Those people back there, they are not my parents.
实在不好意思啊 那些人 根本就不是我父母
- What are you talking about?  - They're not my parents.
- 什么?  - 他们不是我父母
- Those are not your parents?  - No.
- 他们不是你父母?  - 不是
I wanted you to think that I had a perfect family, so I hired some people.
我想让你觉得我有一个美满的家庭 所以我雇了那些人
- You hired people?  - Yes.
那些人是你雇来的?  - 是的
- You hired what kind of people?  - Actors. Actors.
- 你雇的都是些什么三教九流啊?  - 演员 演员
Tuck, this is just bizarre. I don't know what to say about that.
塔克 刚刚真是太离谱了 我都无语了
I don't have any parents. I have no family.
我没有父母 没有家庭
- What?  - I thought it would impress you.
- 什么?  - 我只想给你留个好印象
Okay? That's why I hired some, because I thought that was normal. I thought...
所以我才雇了这些人 我本以为他们挺靠谱的 我以为...
But you have a family. You have a son.
但是你有家庭啊 你儿子都有了
Yeah.
是啊
Okay, the truth about Joe is that my relationship with Joe is really awful.
好吧 实际上我和乔的关系挺差的
It's really awful.
真的很差
When he was a little boy, it was great. He was a puppy.
他小时候 关系是不错 他也很听话
He loved me to bits. Then he grew up, now I can't reach him.
他也超爱我 但是长大后 我就没办法和他沟通了
He doesn't want anything to do with me, at all.
他不想和我扯上任何关系
Okay? So I didn't want you to see that. It's actually very embarrassing.
我不想让你知道这些 真的很丢人
So I thought I'd hire a family, because I thought that was normal.
于是我就想雇人扮演我的家人 我觉得这样比较正常
Right, look, I totally understand you needing to walk away...
好的 我完全理解你为何要走...
because if I were you, I'd walk away too.
因为如果是我 我也会立马就走
But I think... I needed to level with... Yes?  - Tuck.
但我觉得...我还是有必要和你解释清楚...怎么?  - 塔克
It's just I was really looking forward to today.
我本来很期待这一天的
It's just been a lot, and I think I should go.
今天发生太多事了 我真的想走了
Lauren, I really want to get you home safe. Okay, so Joe's is just on the way.
劳伦 我真的很想安全送你回家 但乔已经在来的路上了
Let me pick him up, and then I'll drop you straight off after.
我去接他一下 然后再送你回去好吗
- Okay.  - Thank you.
- 好吧  - 太感谢了
詹姆斯・门罗小学
Hey, Mom, I'm coming!
嘿 妈妈 我来了!
Hey, spudley, how you doing? Come on, give us a cuddle.
嘿 斯巴德雷 你还好吗? 过来让我抱下
Hello.
你好
This is my friend Lauren.
这是我朋友 劳伦
I thought Uncle Frank was your only friend.
我还以为只有弗兰克叔叔是你的朋友呢
Who's Uncle Frank?
弗兰克叔叔是谁?
Yes. Ha, ha. Um.... Ahem.
是啊 哈哈 嗯... 嗯
He's right. He is my only friend from work.
他说得对 我工作上的朋友只有他
But this is my new friend. Lauren.
但这是我的新朋友 劳伦
- Hi.  - Hi.
- 嗨  - 嗨
Hey, what are you two doing this afternoon?
嘿 你们今天下午有空吗?
I need some help with work.
我工作需要帮忙
- You could be the men for the job.  - No.
- 你们是最佳人选  - 不是吧
- Yeah?  - That sounds great.
- 怎么?  - 听起来不错
- Hands up.  - No.
- 举起手来  - 不
# Now I've got a woman #
我现在有了心爱的女人
# She's got a magic spell on me #
我对她非常地迷恋
Go to sat cam 6.
切换6号监控
Bye, Lauren.
再见 劳伦
Hello.
你好
# Now I've got a woman #
我现在有了心爱的女人
He just used the kid.
他利用小孩
He used the kid.
他竟然利用小孩
Maybe we could get you a kid, sir. For a day.
我们也可以给你找个孩子 让你用一天
- You know a guy?  - I know a guy.
- 你认识人吗?  - 我认识
No.
算了吧
# She's got a magic spell on me #
我对她非常地迷恋
I had a really fantastic day today, thank you very much.
我今天过得真的很开心 谢谢你
So did I.
我也很开心
Good night.
晚安
# I got no beef with repetition #
我从不埋怨别人絮絮叨叨
Go inside. Go inside the house.
切进去 切换到室内监控
You don't wanna see the... Oh, my God.
还是别看了吧... 哦 天啊
# I got no beef with repetition #
我从不埋怨别人絮絮叨叨
Bring up 5.
切换到5号
- Two...  - Where did they go? Bring up 3.
- 2号...  - 人呢? 切换到3号
Tuck, we need to talk.
塔克 我有话跟你说
In a little bit.
稍等一会儿
- It's dead. He's killing our bugs.  - Bring up 4.
- 不行 他弄坏了所有的监控  - 切换到4号
There goes 7.
7号
This is so bad.
真的不能这样
But it feels so good.
但感觉太爽了
We're dead, sir.
没信号了 先生
Yeah, we are.
是啊
- Okay, Tuck.  - Mm-hm.
- 好了 塔克  - 嗯
Tuck. Tuck, I'm sorry.
塔克 塔克 对不起
I'm not this kind of girl.
我不是那种女人
I know exactly what kind of girl you are.
我知道你是什么样的人
And that's why I've completely fallen in love with you.
因此我才会全心全意的爱上你
Damn. I think that's the new British Invasion...
该死 我觉得那里肯定又发生了...
what happened there, that's what that was.
新一轮的英国入侵 一定是这样的
I feel like I'm having a panic attack.  - Breathe.
我感觉我恐慌症又发作了  - 深呼吸
Breathe in and breathe out, and come sit down.
好好喘口气 过来坐下
Do you think it's possible to love two people equally?
你觉得 同样爱上两个人可能吗?
Love, yes.
爱 可能
Be in love, no.
爱情 不可能
What do you do when you don't know what to do?
当你不知所措时 你都做些什么?
I ask Bob.
我会问鲍勃
Your husband, Bob?
你丈夫 鲍勃?
- "Bob" Bob?  - Yeah.
- "鲍勃"鲍勃?  - 嗯
I mean, I know he's fat and ridiculous, but he's my fat...
我是说 我知道他很肥 而且还很无厘头 但这些都是...
and my ridiculous.
我生活中的一部分
And I like the way that I am with him.
我喜欢跟他在一起
Mom, could you fix this?  - Hey, buddy.
妈妈 你能修好吗?  - 嘿 宝贝
Don't choose the better guy.
不用想着谁更好
Choose the guy that's gonna make you the better girl.
选那个能让你变得更好的人
- Right?  - Right.
- 是不是?  - 是的
I love you?
我爱你?
Pretty fancy words to get the girl in bed. Bravo. Well done. Good performance.
是骗女孩子上床的好借口 真有你的 干得好 演得真棒
- I don't expect you to understand.  - Why can't you just admit you lost?
- 我不指望你能明白  - 你就不能承认你输了吗?
I didn't. I was doing well until you turned up with your big hair and your white teeth.
我没输 我一直都做得很好 直到你盯着鸡窝头 呲着白牙出现
As per usual.
跟平常一样
- Let's not forget, yes, I did find her first.  - Yeah, but she fell for me, Tuck.
- 别忘了 没错 是我先发现她的  - 没错 她先爱上我的 塔克
She fell for me. It's not my fault you're always a step behind.
她先爱上我的 你一直都慢一拍 又不是我的错
If I'm only a step behind, it's because I'm cleaning up after you.
如果我慢一拍 那是因为我总是给你收拾残局
Do you know what?
知道吗?
I couldn't give a monkey who Lauren chooses between us.
劳伦选择我们两个谁 我都不在乎
But this, what we had....
但这件事 我们两个...
- Yeah, what?  - It's over.
- 嗯 怎么?  - 我们完了
I already asked Collins for a transfer.
我已经跟科林说了 我要转走
- Lauren. How are you? Are you well?  - Hi. Oh, I'm pretty good.
- 劳伦 你怎么样了? 还好吗?  - 嗨 哦 我很好
- Good.  - Are you busy?
- 那就好  - 你忙吗?
- No, no, I'm just at work.  - What are you doing?
- 不 不 我刚刚开始工作  - 你在干什么?
Oh, nothing much. A bit boring, to be honest.
哦 没干什么 说实话 有点无聊
- Do you know that new place on Third?  - I know it very well.
- 你知道3号街的那个新店吗?  - 我知道
- Can you meet me there?  - I can be there in half an hour.
- 能到那里见我吗?  - 我半个小时到
- Okay. I'll see you for lunch then.  - That would be lovely.
- 好的 中午见  - 太好了
- I'll see you there.  - All right, my love.
- 到时见  - 好的 亲爱的
- Bye.  - Bye.
- 再见  - 再见
She called you.
她给你打电话了
Gotta go, mate.
我要走了 伙计
Have to pack up anyway.
反正我还得收拾一下
Lucky water bottle.
幸运的水瓶
Anyway, she is a brilliant mother.
不管怎样 她都是个杰出的母亲
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?
Just watching last night's surveillance video on Tuck.
看昨晚关于塔克的监控录像
Time to close the books on that one, Dickerman. She got away.
是时候翻篇儿了 迪克曼 我没追到她
All right, Dick, I'll see you when I see you.
好了 迪克 我们下次见
I had a really fantastic day today. Thank you very, very much.
今天我非常开心 非常谢谢你
- So did I. It was fun.  - It was.
- 我也是 今天很开心  - 是啊
I, well...
我 恩...
- Scroll back for a second.  - Yeah, so...
- 向后退一秒钟  - 是 那...
- Now zoom in.  - There?
- 放大  - 这儿吗?
No, no, on the background.
不 不 他们后面
Freeze that and enhance.
定格 放大
That's Heinrich.
那是 海因里希
He's here. I have to get Tuck.
他来了 我得去找塔克
I'm really glad you called.
你打电话给我 我真开心
I didn't expect you to. It was a surprise.
我想到你会打给我 真是个惊喜
- Really?  - Yeah.
- 真的吗?  - 是啊
Which is great, because I love surprises.
太好了 因为我喜欢惊喜
You do? Gosh, I don't.
是吗? 天啊 我可不喜欢
Usually, they turn out more bad than...
通常 惊喜都不怎么...
Good grief.
天啊
- Hi.  - Hi.
- 嗨  - 嗨
FDR, what are you...?
富兰克林 你来...?
Uh, I'm sorry. Tuck, this is my friend FDR.
呃 抱歉 塔克 这是我朋友富兰克林
FDR, this is Tuck.
富兰克林 这位是塔克
- Hello, it's lovely to meet you.  - Lovely to meet you.
- 你好 见到你很开心  - 见到你我也很开心
- Are you British?  - Yes, I am.
- 你是英国人吗?  - 是的 我是
That's a crying shame.
真是奇耻大辱啊
- Why?  - Oh, no reason.
- 为什么?  - 哦 没为什么
You have... You have very gentle hands, don't you?
你的手... 你的手非常柔软是不是?
- Strong hands.  - Gentle hands.
- 是强壮的手  - 是柔软的手
- Strong hands.  - Gentle hands. It's like holding a salmon.
- 是强壮的手  - 还是柔软的手 就像三文鱼一样柔软
Can you excuse me for just a second? I'm just gonna, um....
抱歉失陪一下 我得去 嗯...
Just a minute, for a second.
就一分钟 一下
Order me a drink.
给我点杯东西喝
In a shot. I'll be right back.
我马上就回来
# Oh, so horny #
哦 饥渴难耐
- Hello.  - Trish.
- 你好  - 嘿 翠西
They're both here. You gotta get over here. I'm hyperventilating.
他们俩个都在 你赶紧过来 我快喘不过气来了
I told you you shouldn't date two guys at the same time.
我告诉过你不要脚踏两条船
What?
什么?
You have neither the grace nor the humility to lose like a man, do you?
作为一个男人 你就不能失败的时候有点度量和谦卑
It's Heinrich.
是关于海因里希的事
He's in L.A. We have to get on it right now.
他在洛杉矶 我们必须马上搞定他
You know, you are incredible. Really, you are.
你知道吗 你这个人真是不可思议 真的
I have to take my hat off to you. This is impressive.
我都得脱帽向你致敬了 你真是太了不起了
- Listen.  - You take your hands off me.
- 听我说  - 你别碰我
- This is not... Tuck. Tuck.  - Take your hand off me, mate.
- 这不是... 塔克 塔克  - 我说你别碰我
Yeah?
行吗?
- Yeah, all right.  - Where you going? Hey, where you going?
- 行 没问题  - 你去哪儿? 嘿 你要去哪儿?
Hm?
嗯?
You can do this. You are a confident woman who can deal with conflict.
你可以做到的 你是个自信的女人 可以解决任何矛盾
I'm gonna pass out.
我要晕倒了
Has that been on my teeth the whole time?
那菜叶一直在我牙上吗?
Get out there. Tell them your decision. They're rational.
现在出去 告诉他们你的决定 他们是理智的
They may even become friends.
或许他们还能成为朋友呢
They'll probably just shake hands.
他们或许会握手示好
My boobs are sweating.
我胸都出汗了
I should have killed you in Kandahar when I had the chance.
我本该在坎大哈就杀了你
What? Were you having a laugh, mate?
什么? 你在开玩笑吧 朋友?
I was the only thing keeping you alive in Kandahar, mate.
就是有我在 你在坎大哈才没挂 朋友
I was your only friend.
我是你唯一的朋友
Friend?
朋友?
- You two know each other?  - Well, Lauren....
- 你俩认识?  - 嗯 劳伦...
- You two know each other?  - Yes.
- 你俩认识?  - 是
What was this? Some sort of bet? Some sort of game?
这算什么? 你们在打赌吗? 还是在玩我?
To see who could get the girl first?
看谁能最先得到我?
- No, no, no.  - Lauren...
- 不 不是  - 劳伦等等...
- ...let me explain.  - Let me explain.
- ...听我解释  - 听我解释
- I'm really... No, actually... You've done...  - Lauren, listen... Shut up.
- 我真的... 不是 其实... 你已经...  - 劳伦 听我说... 你先住嘴
I trusted you.
我本来很信任你俩的
Lauren. Lauren.
劳伦 等等 劳伦
It's worse than I thought. They know each other.
比我想象的还糟糕 他们居然认识
- What?  - I don't know how.
- 什么?  - 我不知道他们怎么认识的
I got... I walked in and they said they were friends or something.
我... 我下楼就听见他们说他们是朋友之类的
Here, drink this.
给 喝口这个
- Oh, my God, what is that?  - It's a screwdriver.
- 哦 我的天 这是什么?  - 是伏特加橙汁鸡尾酒啦
I mean it's mostly vodka.
其实大多是伏特加
But I'm sure there's some apple juice or something in there from somewhere.
我肯定里面有一些苹果汁的
I just feel like an idiot. I thought they cared about me. Can we get out of here?
感觉我真傻 我以为他们真的在乎我 我们赶紧走吧?
Yeah, sure, we could just go to a bar... What...?
恩 当然 我们可以去个酒吧... 怎么回事...?
- Oh, my God.  - What...?
- 哦 天啊  - 怎么...?
Excuse me. Is there something I can help you with?
抱歉 请问我有什么可以帮你的吗?
- Just give him your keys.  - I don't want the car.
- 把车钥匙给他  - 我不想要你的车
I want your boyfriends.
我想要你的两个男朋友
Don't talk to me, mate. In fact, don't ever talk to me again. Don't...
别跟我说话 你最好永远都别跟我说话 别...
- Is that Sade?  - Sade is not exclusive, my friend. Jesus.
- 那是萨德的歌吗?  - 萨德的歌又不只有你一个人能听 朋友 天啊
- Ah, look.  - Put it on speaker.
- 啊 看  - 把扬声器打开
All right.
好吧
Hi, Lauren, I'm really, really sorry about what happened.
嗨 劳伦 对于刚才发生的事 真的真的很抱歉
Lauren, it's FDR. I am so sorry about what happened.
劳伦 我是富兰克林 刚才的事非常抱歉
- Would you just be quiet?  - Come on, maybe she wants to talk to me.
- 你能不能安静点?  - 拜托 或许她想跟我说话
Why didn't she call your phone then?
那她为什么不打你电话?
- I don't know.  - Shut up.
- 我不知道  - 闭嘴
You shut up.
你闭嘴
- Lauren...  - No, you shut up.
- 劳伦等等...  - 不 你俩都闭嘴
You two come alone unarmed to Warehouse 22 in San Pedro.
你俩来圣佩德罗的22号仓库 不许带任何武器
Or I'll have to kill your pretty girlfriend and her friend.
否则我杀了你们漂亮的女朋友和她朋友
I see any police any agent within a mile...
如果在一英里以内看到警察或探员...
...you get her head in the mail.
...你就等着替她收尸吧
Be there in an hour.
一个小时内到那儿
If we go to that warehouse, she's not walking out and neither are we.
如果我们去那个仓库 我们几个谁也别想活着走出来
- What is that?  - GPS. I put a sat-tracker on her.
- 那是什么?  - 全球定位系统 我在她身上放了追踪器
You put a sat-tracker on her?
你在她身上放追踪器?
- Of course I did, didn't you?  - No.
- 当然放了 你没放吗?  - 没有
Of course I didn't. I didn't put a sat-tracker on her. That's completely immoral. I put one on her cellphone.
我当然没有 我没在她身上装追踪装置 那太不道德了 我在她手机上装了一个
- Steal this car, Tuck.  - Got it.
- 偷这辆车 塔克  - 知道
- Thank you.  - She's heading eastbound on Venice.
- 多谢了  - 她正在向威尼斯东边移动
- Try not to screw this up.  - You try not to screw this up.
- 你不要搞砸  - 你才不要搞砸
Stop repeating everything that I say.
别再重复我说的话了
FDR, target is holding steady.
富兰克林 目标一直在视线内
One mile to contact.
离你还有一英里
Tuck, negative, 0.8 miles to be precise.
塔克 不对 精确的说还有0.8英里
All right. Get me close. I'm gonna pull a Monte Carlo.
好了 靠近他们 我要跳上那辆车
That's negative, we don't have the angle. You are gonna have to do a reverse Karachi.
不行 角度不对 你得先在咱们车的外面 才能上他们的车
Fine. Just get me close.
好吧 靠近他们的车
No! What are you doing? No!
不! 你们在做什么? 不要啊!
- Trish!  - Got it.
- 翠西!  - 搞定
Shit!
我去!
Drive, you idiot!
开车啊 笨蛋!
What the hell is going on?
到底怎么回事?
I'm gonna be honest with you Lauren. I am not a travel agent.
跟你说实话 劳伦 我不是旅行社代理
- Really?  - I'm not a cruise ship captain.
- 真的吗?  - 我也不是游艇船长
No shit.
我去 你当然不是
Oh, my God!
哦 我的天!
- Oh, God.  - Okay.
- 哦 天啊  - 好了
Grab the wheel, please.
抓好方向盘 拜托
- Girl, I've seen you drive. Take the wheel.  - I'm not gonna drive this car.
- 丫头 我见过你开车 掌好方向盘  - 我不要开这辆车
- Turn around.  - Shit!
- 转弯  - 我靠!
Tuck!
嘿 塔克!
- I missed you.  - I know. I've missed you too.
- 我好怀念你  - 我知道 我也是
- I love you, man.  - Love you too.
- 我爱你 哥们儿  - 我也爱你
- We're back.  - Oh, my God. I'm Yoko.
- 我们又像从前一样了  - 哦 天啊 我成约科了
Good afternoon, I'm Susan Walsh coming to you live from the studio...
下午好 我是苏珊沃尔什 在为您进行现场直播
- Mom.  - Yeah?
- 妈妈  - 嗯?
- Is that Dad?  - Huh?
- 那是爸爸吗?  - 啊?
- Where the hell are they going?  - Headed south on the 310 Freeway.
- 他们到底要去哪儿?  - 沿着310高速公路往南开
But that freeway's incomplete.
但是那条高速公路还没完工
Three hundred feet, 200. They're running out of road.
还有300英尺 200了 马上他们就没路了
I hope you can forgive him, Lauren.
我希望你可以原谅他 劳伦
- He's the best man I know.  - Bollocks, mate.
- 他是我认识的最好的男人  - 胡说
You two belong to each other. You really do, you belong to each other.
你们两个是天生一对 真的 你们两个应该在一起
Tuck, no, Thank you, Tuck, she's already made her choice.
塔克 不 谢谢 塔克 她已经做出选择了
No. No, I didn't.
不 不 我没有
- You didn't?  - You didn't?
- 你没有?  - 你没有?
- What? You didn't?  - No, I mean, I did, but...
- 什么? 你没有?  - 不 我是说 我做出选择了 但是...
- In light of everything I just found out, I feel...  - Tuck.
- 但是面对我刚得知的一切 我感觉...  - 又来了塔克
- It's bulletproof.  - The lights.
- 是防弹的  - 灯
Shoot the headlights.
射车头灯
Front-impact airbag deployment in all models after 2006.
2006年以后所有的车都有防撞击的气袋
- Are you okay?  - Yeah.
- 你还好吧?  - 我没事
- Good.  - Yeah.
- 那就好  - 是啊
I'm okay.
我没事
All right, get a room.
行了 开个房间再亲热吧
- And this time, We do not know how it started.  - I don't think he's a travel agent.
- 这次 不知道是如何引起的  - 我觉得他不是旅行社代理
It may have involved a German terrorist group...
可能跟一名德国恐怖分子有关
...as well as two federal agents.
...还有两名联邦探员卷入其中
- Let me take a look at that, sir?  - No, I'm fine.
- 先生 我看看您的伤口?  - 不用了 我没事
I was gonna tell you. That's why I asked you out.
我本打算告诉你的 所以才叫你出来
Yeah, it's okay. I, um....
恩 没关系 我 呃...
It's good. It's good. I understand.
挺好的 挺好的 我明白
- Okay.  - It's good.
- 那就好  - 挺好的
Does Joe know about this?
乔知道吗?
Um....
嗯...
No.
不知道
No, not yet, but I think he will in a minute.
还不知道 但我想他很快就知道了
All right.
好吧
I should... I should probably... I should probably head off.
我应该... 我大概应该... 我大概应该撤了
Okay.
好的
Good.
好
Take care.
保重
Hey, Tuck.
嘿 塔克
I'll, uh, take care of all this.
我 呃 我搞定这儿吧
Thank you.
谢谢
All right.
好的
I'll see you... I'll see you in the office?
我们... 我们办公室见?
No.
不
I'll see you in the field, mate.
我们战场上见 哥们儿
- Come here, you.  - Come here, you.
- 过来 抱抱  - 过来 抱抱
- I love you.  - I love you too.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
- You're family always and forever.  - Yeah. So are you.
- 你永远都是我的亲人  - 恩 你也是
- Take care.  - You take care of her.
- 保重  - 好好照顾她
So....
那...
So when I added it all up and I crunched all the numbers, it was a...
当我回头再想想 我想起那些数据 是...
Shh. No more thinking.
嘘 别想了
You're gonna make me regret this, aren't you?
你会让我后悔的 是不是
For the rest of your life.
你会后悔一辈子
Did you see that? You see, it worked.
你看到了吗? 你看 成功了
- It worked. You see that?  - What'd I tell you? Hm?
- 成功了 你看见了吗?  - 我跟你说啥来? 嗯?
You happy? All right, go get your sneakers. Go on.
开心了吧? 好了 去穿鞋吧 快去
- You're not listening to me.  - Mate, can I have a quick word with you?
- 你没听我的话  - 哥们儿 能跟你说两句话吗?
That's it, stand up.
好了 站好
A brave man once said to me, "Pain is weakness leaving the body."
一个勇敢的人曾经对我说 "身体最大的弱点就是怕疼"
Bye, weakness.
再见 弱点
Weakness leaving the body.
身体的弱点
You go on. Talk to your friends for a bit.
去吧 去跟你朋友聊聊天
Hey.
嘿
So you're not a travel agent?
这么说你不是旅行社代理?
- No.  - Mm-hm.
- 不是  - 嗯嗯
Um.... This is me.
嗯... 这就是我
Hi, um, I'm Katie.
嗨 嗯 我是卡蒂
Hello.Katie. I'm Tuck. Pleased to meet you.
你好 卡蒂 我是塔克 很高兴见到你
- Tuck?  - That's right. Yeah.
- 你叫塔克?  - 对 是的
So nice to meet you. Finally.
终于见到你了 很幸会
- You hungry?  - Yes, I am.
- 你饿了吗?  - 是 我饿了
Well, you wanna get some dinner? As a family?
你想一起吃饭吗? 我们一家人?
Yes, yes, I would.
是 是 我想一起吃
Okay, good.
好的
Okay, bud, time to go.
好了 小家伙 该走了
Hello?
你好?
Hey, babe, you're using the vector chute, right?
嘿 宝贝 你用的是无线电降落伞吗?
Yeah, of course.
是啊 当然
It's got high-tensile fiber and triple-secure locking features.
有高强度纤维和三重安全锁定功能
It gets fives across the board.
综合来看 它可以得五颗星
Oh, God, I love it when you talk dirty.
哦 天啊 我喜欢你挑逗我
Ha, ha. Oh, Nana's tomorrow night. Don't forget to tell Tuck to bring Katie and Joe.
哈 哈 哦 明晚去奶奶家 别忘了告诉塔克带上卡蒂和乔
- Hey, Nana's tomorrow night, huh?  - Is that Nana you're talking to?
- 嘿 明晚去奶奶家 是吧?  - 你是在跟奶奶说话吗?
No.
不是
Did you tell him yet?
你告诉他了吗?
- I'm just about to.  - Good luck.
- 我正要告诉他  - 祝你好运
I love you, baby.
我爱你 宝贝
- I love you, baby.  - Bye.
- 我爱你 宝贝  - 拜
Ah! I'm gonna throw you the best bachelorette party ever!
啊! 我会给你办个最好的单身派对!
- Are you sure that we should do this?  - Have I ever, ever, ever steered you wrong?
- 你确定我们要这样做吗?  - 什么时候我误导过你?
- Brother.  - Yo.
- 兄弟  - 哟
I asked Lauren to marry me.
我向劳伦求婚了
Will you be my best man?
你会来当我伴郎吗?
- Jump run!  - Hey, you're good.
- 该跳了!  - 嘿 你准备好了
I know it's a little awkward with you having slept with her and everything, but....
我知道你俩上床这件事有些尴尬 但是...
- Don't worry about it, Lauren didn't even...  - I just think it's poetic justice, right?
- 别担心 劳伦甚至还没...  - 我觉得你应有此报 对吧?
What is?
什么意思?
Well, I've been meaning to tell you this for a while, but I slept with Katie.
嗯 我一直都想告诉你来 我跟卡蒂上过床
Once. It was long time ago. Before you guys even knew each other.
有一次 很久之前的事了 你俩还没认识对方
- Slept with my wife?  - She wasn't. You didn't know her.
- 你跟我妻子上床?  - 她当时还不是你妻子 你当时不认识她
- You slept with my wife?  - It was a long time ago, man.
- 你跟我妻子上床?  - 那是很久之前的事了
I never even slept with Lauren.
我从未跟劳伦上过床
- What?  - I never slept with Lauren!
- 什么?  - 我从未跟劳伦上过床
No, I only let you think that, right? Think that, to make you jealous.
没有 我只想让你那样想 好不好? 让你嫉妒
- You never slept with Lauren?  - You slept with my wife!
- 你从未跟劳伦上过床?  - 你跟我妻子上过床!